<resources>
    <!--APP Name-->
    <string name="app_name">HKUEEE</string>

    <!--Teacher information, 42 teachers-->
    <string name="te1">Prof. S.C.Chan</string>
    <string name="te2">Prof. K.T.Chau</string>
    <string name="te3">Dr. V.W.L.Tam</string>
    <string name="te4">Dr. W.W.T.Fok</string>
    <string name="te5">Dr. Y.C.Wu</string>
    <string name="te6">Dr. Q.Chen</string>
    <string name="te7">Prof. G.Chesi</string>
    <string name="te8">Dr. A.H.W.Choi</string>
    <string name="te9">Prof. W.C.H.Choy</string>
    <string name="te10">Prof. L.K.Yeung</string>

    <string name="te11">Dr. Zhiqin Chu</string>
    <string name="te12">Prof. D.J.Hill</string>
    <string name="te13">Dr. Y.Hou</string>
    <string name="te14">Dr. K.B.Huang</string>
    <string name="te15">Prof. R.S.Y.Hui</string>
    <string name="te16">Dr. L.Jiang</string>
    <string name="te17">Prof. R.Y.K.Kwok</string>
    <string name="te18">Prof. P.T.Lai</string>
    <string name="te19">Prof. E.Y.M.Lam</string>
    <string name="te20">Dr. J.C.K.Lam</string>

    <string name="te21">Dr. K.H.Lam</string>
    <string name="te22">Dr. W.H.Lam</string>
    <string name="te23">Dr. C.K.Lee</string>
    <string name="te24">Ir W.K.Lee</string>
    <string name="te25">Dr. W.N.Lee</string>
    <string name="te26">Dr. K.C.Leung</string>
    <string name="te27">Dr. K.H.Li</string>
    <string name="te28">Prof. V.O.K.Li</string>
    <string name="te29">Dr. T.Liu</string>
    <string name="te30">Dr. K.S.Lui</string>

    <string name="te32">Ir Dr.M.H.Pong</string>
    <string name="te31">Dr. G.K.H.Pang</string>
    <string name="te33">Dr. P.W.T.Pong</string>
    <string name="te34">Dr. H.K.H.So</string>
    <string name="te35">Prof. S.C.Tan</string>
    <string name="te36">Prof. N.C.Tien</string>
    <string name="te37">Dr. K.K.M.Tsia</string>
    <string name="te38">Prof. K.K.Y.Wong</string>dir
    <string name="te39">Dr. N.Wong</string>
    <string name="te40">Prof. E.X.Wu</string>

    <string name="te41">Dr. J.C.H.Yuen</string>
    <string name="te42">Dr. J.Zhong</string>
    <!--teacher information-->
    <string name="teinfo0">Prof. S.C. Chan\n\n
    Professor\nAssociate Head (TPG and Development)\n\nB.Sc.(Eng.), Ph.D. H.K.; M.I.E.E.E.\nEmail: scchan@eee.hku.hk\nTel.: 2859-8025\nOffice: CB 721\n\nResearch Interests\n\nS. C. Chan received his B.Sc (Eng) and Ph.D degrees from the University of Hong Kong in 1986 and 1992, respectively. He joined City Polytechnic of Hong Kong at 1990 as an assistant Lecturer and later as a University Lecturer. Since 1994, he has been with the department of electrical and electronic engineering, the University of Hong Kong, and is now a Professor. He held visiting positions in Microsoft Corporation, Redmond, USA, Microsoft Research Asia, University of Texas at Arlington, and Nanyang Technological University.\n\nProf. Chan’s main research area is signal processing and applications. His previous research covers fast transform algorithms, filter design and realization, multirate and array signal processing, adaptive and communications signal processing, data compression and image-based rendering, high-speed signal converters, biomedical signal processing and bioinformatics. His research sponsors include the HK Research Grant Council (RGC) and the innovative technology fund (ITF) of HK.\n\nProf. Chan has served in a number of professional and administrative committees. He is currently a member of the Digital Signal Processing Technical Committee of the IEEE Circuits and Systems Society, Associate Editors for IEEE Trans. Circuits and Systems I and Journal of Signal Processing systems, and was the Chairman of the IEEE HK Chapter of Signal Processing. He was the special session chairman of ICASSP2003 and is an organizing committee member of the IEEE 2010 ICIP.\n\nProf. Chan has published more than 200 journal and conference articles and is the co-author of a book: image-based rendering by Springer, 2006.
    </string>


    <string name="teinfo1">
    Prof. K.T. Chau\n\nProfessor\nHead of Department\n\nB.Sc. (Eng.), M.Phil., Ph.D. H.K.; C.Eng., F.I.E.E.E., F.I.E.T., F.H.K.I.E.\nEmail: ktchau@eee.hku.hk\nWeb: https://www.eee.hku.hk/~ktchau\nTel.: 2859-2704\nOffice: CB 709\n\nResearch Interests\n\nElectric Vehicle Technologies, Renewable Energy Systems, Machines and Drives, Power Electronics\n\nIr Professor K.T. Chau received his B.Sc.(Eng.) degree with First Class Honours, M.Phil. degree, and Ph.D. degree all in Electrical &amp; Electronic Engineering from The University of Hong Kong. He joined the alma mater in 1995, and has served as Director of the International Research Centre for Electric Vehicles, and Associate Dean of Engineering (Teaching and Learning – Taught Postgraduate). Currently, he serves as Professor and Head of Department in the Department of Electrical &amp; Electronic Engineering.\n\nHe is a Chartered Engineer, Fellow of the IET, and Fellow of the HKIE. He is elected Fellow of the IEEE for Contributions to Energy Systems for Electric and Hybrid Vehicles. He has served as chairs and organizing committee members for many international conferences, especially in the area of Electric Vehicles. Currently, he serves as Editor of the Studies in Science and Technology, Co-Editor of the Journal of Asian Electric Vehicles, Section Editor-in-Chief of the Energies, and Editorial Board Member of some international journals. He is also an international consultant for electric vehicle technologies. Professor Chau has published 7 books, 9 book chapters and over 270 refereed journal papers as well as many conference papers and industrial reports. His teaching philosophy follows the Confucian classic “Li Ji” – Teaching and learning are mutually motivating.\n\nProfessor Chau has received many awards: including the Chang Jiang Chair Professorship by the Ministry of Education, China; Natural Science Award (First Prize) by the Ministry of Education, China; the Environmental Excellence in Transportation Award for Education, Training and Public Awareness by the Society of Automotive Engineers (SAE) International; the Award for Innovative Excellence in Teaching, Learning and Technology at the International Conference on College Teaching and Learning; and the University Teaching Fellow Award by The University of Hong Kong. Currently, he serves as IEEE Vehicular Technology Society (VTS) Distinguished Lecturer.\n\nIn community service, he has served as Member of the Electrical Safety Advisory Committee for the Electrical and Mechanical Services Department, Member of the Accreditation Advisory Board for the Hong Kong Accreditation Service of Innovation and Technology Commission, Member of the Appeal Board Panel under Energy Efficiency (Labelling of Products) Ordinance, Member of the Disciplinary Tribunal Panel under Electricity Ordinance, and Member of the Disciplinary Board Panel under Building Energy Efficiency (Registered Energy Assessors) Regulation. He has also served as Member of Engineering Panel for the Hong Kong Research Grants Council (RGC), Member of Innovation and Technology Support Program Panel for the Innovation and Technology Fund (ITF), and Member of Incu-Tech/ Incu-Bio Technology Program Panel for the Hong Kong Science and Technology Parks (HKSTP).

    </string>


    <string name="teinfo2">
    Dr. V.W.L. Tam\n\nPrincipal Lecturer\n\nBA (CompStud) HK; M.Phil (CS) HK; Ph.D. (CS) Australia\nEmail: vtam@eee.hku.hk\nTel.: 2859-2697\nOffice: CB 707\n\nResearch Interests\n\nAd-hoc and wireless sensor networks, human-computer interaction, ubiquitous computing and learning, I.C.T. in education. Before joining the University of Hong Kong, Vincent was an academic fellow in the School of Computing, the National University of Singapore from 1998 until 2001. During this period, Vincent was the winner of the Innovative Teaching Award – 2000 among 80+ teaching staff in the School of Computing. In 2010-11, Vincent was awarded with the Best Teacher Award in the Faculty of Engineering, the University of Hong Kong. Dr. Tam has over 70 internationally refereed publications, including 5 book chapters, 10+ journal papers and 50+ conference papers. His main research interests include information visualization, mobile computing and wireless sensors, in which he established collaboration with famous institutions in Australia, England, Japan and the U.S.A. Besides, Dr. Tam is interested to apply the latest wireless or interactive technologies for developing useful educational software and their sound applications in e-learning. Furthermore, he is active in serving international conferences and reviewing for reputable journals. Vincent served as the Publication Chair of ICTAI’05, the Co-organizer of a Special Session in CCNC 2008, the Guest Editor of a Special Issue in the IEEE Learning Technology Newsletter and also the PC members of the IEEE International Conference on Tools with Artificial Intelligence (ICTAI’00 – ’07, except ’02), the Asia Pacific Symposium on Information Visualization (APVIS 2006 and 2007), the International Conference on ICT in Teaching and Learning (ICT 2006 – 2009), the IEEE Global Communications Conference (GLOBECOM) 2007,  the IEEE Consumer Communications and Networking Conference (CCNC 2007 – 2010), and the IEEE International Symposium on Communications and Information Technologies (ISCIT 2007 – 2009). Vincent is the Principal Investigators (PIs) or Co-Investigators of various university-funded or externally awarded research projects, including a research project entitled “An Innovative and Pen-Based COMPAD Platform to Enhance Education and Research in Computer Systems” awarded by the Microsoft Research Asia (MSRA) under the Mobile Computing in Education Theme 2008. In recognition of his experience in managing e-learning related projects, the EDB invited him to serve as the (part-time) Project Manager of an EMB project for developing E-Learning Training Package to support all AS-level Computer Applications and AL-level Computer Studies teachers in Hong Kong in 2006, and later as the (part-time) Deputy Project Director of another EDB-funded project for developing learning and teaching packages to support the ICT Elective of the New Senior Secondary (NSS) curriculum. In 2008, Vincent and his team won the Bronze Award of the ICT 2008 Awards – Best Lifestyle supported by the HKSAR Government. Vincent is a Senior Member of the IEEE (SMIEEE) – Hong Kong Section. Moreover, he is listed in the Marquis’s 9th Edition of “Who’s Who in Science and Engineering” (September 2006), and also invited to be listed in “Who’s Who in Asia” (Premier Edition, December 2006). For detail, check Dr. Tam’s personal webpage at: https://www.eee.hku.hk/~vtam
    </string>


    <string name="teinfo3">
    Dr. W.W.T. Fok\n\nPrincipal Lecturer\nAssistant Dean of Engineering\n\nB.Eng., M.Sc.(Engg), M.Sc. (Env Mgnt), MBA, Ph.D, CEng, MHKIE.\nEmail:wtfok@eee.hku.hk\nWeb: https://www.eee.hku.hk/~wtfok\nURL of the e-Learning Development Laboratory: http://elearning.eee.hku.hk\nTel.: 28578490 / 93676877\nOffice: CB 703\n\nResearch Interests\n\nE- Learning technologies and application\E-Commerce and mobile commerce technologies\Engineering Economics and Finance\Clean Energy and Environment\n\nDr. Fok is a Chartered Engineer and he received his B.Eng degree in Electrical and Electronics Engineering from the University of Hong Kong in 1993. Dr. Fok also received two other M.Sc. degrees in Industrial Engineering and Environmental Management from this University in 1996 and 1999 respectively. In 1998 and 2007, he also awarded a MBA degree and a PhD degree from the University of Cambridge and Renmin University of China respectively.\n\nDr. Fok is the Convener of the Sichuan Reconstruction Project since 2009. He led students to Sichuan to serve in school reconstruction projects. He also supervised the e-Learning Development Laboratory which has developed many innovative e-learning technologies and won a few Hong Kong ICT Awards since 2011. Dr. Fok received the Best Teacher Award in 2010, Outstanding Teaching Team Award in 2013, Knowledge Exchange Award in 2014 and Outstanding Teaching Award in 2015.\n\nMore information about Dr. Fok are available at: https://www.eee.hku.hk/~wtfok\n\nProfessional Services\n\nTown Planning Board, Hong Kong Special Administration Region (2012-present)\nAppeal Tribunal, Buildings Ordinance, Building Department, HKSAR (2013-present)\nExecutive, Hong Kong Institutions of Engineers, 2013-2014\nMember, Engineering Registration Board\nChairman, HKIE Electronics Division, 2008-09\nHKU Convocation Standing Committee (2006-2015)\nHKU Court Member (2009-2015)\nVice-President, Hong Kong University Graduates Association (2003-2008)\nCore Member, Initiative on Clean Energy and Environment \n
    </string>

    <string name="teinfo4">
    Dr. Y.C. Wu\n\nAssociate Professor\n\nB.Eng., M.Phil. HK; Ph.D. Texas A&amp;M\nEmail:ycwu@eee.hku.hk\nWeb: https://www.eee.hku.hk/~ycwu\nTel.: 2859-7090\nOffice: CB 714\n\nResearch Interests\n\nMachine Learning, Signal Processing, Communication Systems\n\nYik-Chung Wu received the B.Eng. (EEE) degree in 1998 and the M.Phil. degree in 2001 from the University of Hong Kong (HKU).  He received the Croucher Foundation scholarship in 2002 to study Ph.D. degree at Texas A&amp;M University, College Station, and graduated in 2005.  From August 2005 to August 2006, he was with the Thomson Corporate Research, Princeton, NJ, as a Member of Technical Staff.  Since September 2006, he has been with HKU, currently as an Associate Professor.  He was a visiting scholar at Princeton University, in summers of 2011 and 2015.\n\nHis research interests are in general areas of machine learning, signal processing and communication systems, and in particular distributed signal processing, Bayesian inference and optimization theories.  Dr. Wu served as an Editor for IEEE Communications Letters, is currently an Editor for IEEE Transactions on Communications and Journal of Communications and Networks.  He was a TPC member for over 50 IEEE major conferences.  He received three best paper awards in international conferences.  He is a senior member of the IEEE.
    </string>

    <string name="teinfo5">Dr. Q. Chen\n\nResearch Assistant Professor\n\nB.Sc., M.Phil., Ph.D.\nEmail:quanchen@eee.hku.hk\nTel.: 2857-8495\nOffice: CB 521\n\nResearch Interests\n\nMulti-physics and Multi-scale Modeling and Simulation; Electronic design automation; Numerical methods for large-scale scientific computing; Applied Electromagnetics; Parallel computing.\n\nDr. Quan Chen received the B.Sc. degree in Electronic Engineering from the Sun Yat-Sen University, China. He obtained the M. Phil. and Ph. D. degree in electronic engineering from The University of Hong Kong, Hong Kong, in 2007 and 2010, respectively.\n\nFrom 2010 to 2011, he was a postdoctoral fellow in the department of Computer Science and Engineering of the University of California, San Diego. He worked as a postdoctral fellow in the department of Electrical and Electronic Engineering of The University of Hong Kong from 2011 to 2012, where he is now a Research Assistant Professor.\n\nDr. Chen’s main research interest is in the multi-physics and multi-scale modeling of microelectronic systems. He has been working closely with research groups in the Faculty of Science, HKU in the UGC Area of Excellence, Theory, Modeling, and Simulation of Emerging Electronics, since 2009, primarily on the combination of semi-classical semiconductor device model with quantum mechanical model. Dr. Chen is a member of IEEE. He served regularly as the reviewers of several journals, such as IEEE transactions on Computer-Aided Design for Integrated Circuits, Advanced Packaging and Magnetics.
    </string>

    <string name="teinfo6">
    Prof. G. Chesi\n\nProfessor\n\nLaurea (Florence), PhD (Bologna), F.I.E.E.E.\nEmail:chesi@eee.hku.hk\nWeb: https://www.eee.hku.hk/~chesi/\nTel.: 2219-4362\nOffice: CB 502\n\nResearch Interests\n\n2D systems, Computer vision, Networked control systems, Nonlinear control, Robust control, SOS, Visual servoing.\n\nGraziano Chesi received the Laurea from the University of Florence in 1997 and the Ph.D. from the University of Bologna in 2001. He joined the University of Siena in 2000 and the University of Hong Kong in 2006.\n\nProf. Chesi served as Associate Editor for Automatica, the European Journal of Control, the IEEE Transactions on Automatic Control, the IEEE Transactions on Computational Biology and Bioinformatics, and Systems and Control Letters. He also served as Guest Editor for the IEEE Transactions on Automatic Control, the International Journal of Robust and Nonlinear Control, and Mechatronics.\n\nProf. Chesi founded and served as chair of the Technical Committee on Systems with Uncertainty of the IEEE Control Systems Society. He also served as chair of the Best Student Paper Award Committees for the IEEE Conference on Decision and Control and the IEEE Multi-Conference on Systems and Control.\n\nProf. Chesi is author of two books and editor of one book, all published by Springer. He is first author in more than 160 peer-reviewed publications. Since 2012, he is in the Top 1% HKU Scholars (most-cited scientists according to Thomson Reuter’s Essential Science Indicators). He is a Fellow of the IEEE.
    </string>
    <string name="teinfo7">
    Dr. A.H.W. Choi\n\nAssociate Professor\n\nBEng., Ph.D., Sen.M.I.E.E.E.\nEmail:hwchoi@eee.hku.hk\nWeb: https://www.eee.hku.hk/~hwchoi/\nTel.: 2859-2693\nOffice: CB 716\n\nResearch Interests\n\nGallium Nitride materials/ device design, modeling, processing and characterization\n\nAnthony Choi is associate professor with the Department of Electrical and Electronic Engineering at The University of Hong Kong. Dr. Choi received his PhD from the National University of Singapore under the supervision of Professor Soo Jin Chua and completed his postdoctoral training in Professor Martin Dawson’s team at the University of Strathclyde, Glasgow, where he contributed to pioneering development work on III-Nitride emissive micro-light-emitting diode arrays, demonstrating applications in the areas of micro-displays and high-efficiency light sources.\n\nAt the Semiconductor Lighting and Display Laboratory, Dr. Choi leads a team of researchers investigating contemporary and intriguing research topics which include solid-state lighting, optical resonance and micro-cavities, nanophotonics, and laser processing of optical materials. His major contributions include using the design and implementation of the stacked LED structure for polychromatic or color-tunable emission, 3-D shaping of LED chips with laser processes as well as GaN-on-Si pivoted microcavities.\n\nHe has published over 200 papers in leading journals and international conferences, edited a book volume entitled “Handbook of Optical Microcavities”, contributed to 3 book chapters, holds numerous US and PCT patents and is actively involved in professional activities, such as serving as chairperson for the international conferences LEDsAsia 2009 and EDSSC 2010.
    </string>
    <string name="teinfo8">
    Prof. W.C.H. Choy\n\nProfessor\n\nMPhil, HK; PhD, Surrey, OSA Fellow, Senior M.I.E.E.E., C.Eng., M.I.E.T.\nEmail:chchoy@eee.hku.hk\nWeb: https://www.eee.hku.hk/~chchoy-group/\nTel.: 2857-8485\nOffice: CB 702\nResearch Interests\n\nResearch Interest: the design, physics, and mechanism of organic/inorganic optoelectronic devices; plasmonic nanostructures, nanoscale structures and the hybrid systems with organic/inorganic materials; the multi-physical (optical, electrical and thermal) properties and applications of the hybrid systems.\n\nWallace C. H. Choy received his PhD Degree in Electronic Engineering from the University of Surrey, UK in 1999. He then joined National Research Council of Canada as a member of research staff to work on optical device structures of polarization independent optical amplifiers and modulators. He joined Fujitsu at San Jose, US in 2001 to develop real-time wavelength tunable lasers and optical transmitter modules.\n\nHe is currently a professor of Department of Electrical and Electronic Engineering, the University of Hong Kong (HKU). Dr. Choy has published over 185 internationally peer-reviewed journal papers, contributed to one book and five book chapters, as well as a number of US and China patents. Among his publications, 12 papers have been featured as cover-story articles such as Adv. Mater., Adv Energy Mater., and Chem Comm., and 14 articles have been highlighted in research new/scholarly articles. Details of publication can be found in Google Scholar. He was the recipient of the Sir Edward Youde Memorial Fellowship, the Croucher Foundation Fellowship, and the Outstanding Achievement Award from National Research Council of Canada and HKU Research Output Prize. He received overseas visiting fellowships from HKU to take a sabbatical leave at George Malliaras’s Group, Cornell University in 2008, a visit to Prof. Yang Yang, UCLA in summers of 2009 and 2011, Prof. Karl Leo, Institut fuer Angewandte Photophysik (IAPP), Technische Universitaet Dresden, Germany in the summer of 2010, and Prof./Sir Richard Friend, Cavendish Lab, Cambridge University, UK.\n\nWallace Choy is a fellow of OSA and senior member of IEEE. He is one of 2018 higher cited researchers (in the category of cross-fields) and has been recognized as Top 1% of most-cited scientists in Thomson Reuter’s Essential Science Indicators (ESI) three years in a row 2014, 2015, 2016 and 2017. He has been recognized as prolific researcher on organic solar cells in the index (WFC in physical sciences) in Nature Index 2014 Hong Kong published by Nature. He has served as Member of Engineering panels of Hong Kong Research Grant Council, Editorial Board Member for Nature Publishing Group on Scientific Reports, Wiley on Solar RRL and Institute of Physics on J Physics D, senior editor of IEEE Photonics Journal, topical editor of OSA Journal of the Optical Society of America B (JOSA B; JOSA founded in 1917), and guest editor of OSA Journal of Photonic Research, and Journal of Optical Quantum Electronics. He has delivered over 80 invited talks and served as a committee member in internationally industrial and academic conferences organized by various organizations such as IEEE, OSA and Plastic Electronics Foundation.
    </string>
    <string name="teinfo9">
    Prof. L.K. Yeung\n\nProfessor\nAssociate Head (RPG and Resources)\n\nB.Eng., Ph.D. CUHK, SMIEEE\nEmail:kyeung@eee.hku.hk\nTel.: 2857-8493\nOffice: CB 708\nResearch Interests\n\nNext-generation Internet, packet switch/router design, all-optical networks, wireless data networks.\n\nProf. Yeung was born in 1969. He received his B.Eng. and Ph.D. degrees in Information Engineering from The Chinese University of Hong Kong in 1992 and 1995, respectively. He joined the Department of Electrical and Electronic Engineering, The University of Hong Kong in July 2000, where he is currently a Professor, and the Information Engineering Program Co-Director. Before that, he has spent five years in the Department of Electronic Engineering, City University of Hong Kong as an Assistant Professor. During the summer of 1993, Prof. Yeung served with the Performance Analysis Department, AT&amp;T Bell Laboratories, Holmdel, USA, as a Member of Technical Staff-I. Prof. Yeung’s research interests include next-generation Internet, packet switch/router design, all-optical networks and wireless data networks. Prof. Yeung is a regular technical reviewer for many international journals and conferences, and an associate editor of EURASIP Journal on Wireless Communications and Networking. He has co-authored a book and published over 170 papers in international journals and conferences since 1993. In the academic year of 1998-99, he was recognized as an Outstanding Teacher in the Department of Electronic Engineering, City University of Hong Kong. In the year of 2001-2002, he received the Outstanding Young Researcher Awards from The University of Hong Kong.
    </string>
    <string name="teinfo10">
    Dr. Zhiqin Chu\n\nAssistant Professor (joint appointment with School of Biomedical Sciences)\n\nEmail:zqchu@eee.hku.hk\nTel.: 2859 2685\nOffice: CB516\n\nResearch Interests\n\nDr. Chu received his B.S. and PhD degrees all in Physics from Northwest University (China) and The Chinese University of Hong Kong, in July 2008 and July 2012, respectively. After one year as postdoctoral fellow in the same group, Dr. Chu carried out his postdoctoral research (2014/04-2016/09) at The University of Stuttgart (Germany). Dr. Chu moved back to Hong Kong in October 2016 and worked as a Research Assistant Professor in Department of Physics at The Chinese University of Hong Kong. Since November 2018, Dr. Chu has been an Assistant Professor in Department of Electrical and Electronic Engineering (Joint Appointment with School of Biomedical Sciences) at The University of Hong Kong. Dr. Chu received the Chen Ning Yang Scholarship from The Chinese University of Hong Kong in 2012, and also The Finalist of Hong Kong Young Scientist Awards (under physics track) from The Hong Kong Institution of Science in 2013.
    </string>
    <string name="teinfo11">
    Prof. D.J. Hill\n\nChair of Electrical Engineering\n\nBE (Elec Eng), BSc (Math), PhD; FIEEE, FTSE (Aust Acad Tech Sci and Eng), FAA (Aust Acad Sci), FHKEng; also SIAM Fellow and Fgn Mem Royal Swedish Acad Eng Sci\nEmail:dhill@eee.hku.hk\nTel.: 2859 7092\nOffice: CB 601H\n\nResearch Interests\n\nInterests are in power systems, control systems, complex networks and stability analysis. Current work is mainly on structure, dynamics and control of future energy networks and some basic stability and control questions for dynamic networks.\n\nProfessor David Hill joined the staff of The University of Hong Kong in 2013. He directs the Centre for Electrical Energy Systems (established by Professor Felix Wu in 1996) and is the Project Coordinator for the RGC Theme-based Research Scheme (Round 4) Project on Sustainable Power Delivery Structures for High Renewables (with Co-Is from HKU, HK University of Science and Technology, HK Polytechnic University, Imperial College London and the University of Sydney).\n\nPrior to joining HKU, he held the Chair of Electrical Engineering at The University of Sydney, Australia, initially during 1994-2002 and again 2010-2013 (supported by Ausgrid). He established the Centre for Future Energy Networks (CFEN), and has been Director, 2010-now. During 1996-1999, he served as Head of the School of Electrical and Information Engineering. He has twice held Australian Research Council (ARC) Professorial Fellowships. During 2005-2010, he was an ARC Federation Fellow at the Australian National University (only 25 awarded internationally per year for all areas) and, from 2006, also a Theme Leader (Complex Networks) and Deputy Director in the ARC Centre of Excellence for Mathematics and Statistics of Complex Systems. During  2010-2013, he held an ARC Professorial Fellowship at the University of Sydney. In Sydney, he continues to collaborate with researchers in CFEN on projects in the area of Future Grid, including in the CSIRO University Cluster, 2013-2016, which he played a leading role in establishing.\n\nHe has been continuously associated with Hong Kong universities since 2001 when he was a visiting Professor at City University of HK (CityU). He served on the Panel for Electrical and Electronic Engineering in the University Grants Committee Research Assessment Exercise for 1999. During 2001-2004, he was Chair Professor and Head of the Department of Electronic Engineering at CityU. During 2012-2013, he held a visiting Chair Professorship under the Distinguished Scholars Scheme in the Department of Electronic and Information Engineering at PolyU. He currently holds honorary or adjunct professorships at CityU, South China University of Technology, Wuhan University, Northeastern University, Changsha University of Science and Technology and Chongging University, China.\n\nHe has also held academic and substantial visiting positions at the universities of Melbourne, California (Berkeley), Newcastle (Australia), Lund (Sweden) and Munich (TUM). He has numerous international professional involvements, mainly with IEEE and IFAC as well as independent conferences and workshops including PSCC, IREP and IWCSN.\n\nIn the last few years, he has been invited to speak at several panels and workshops, including at the USA Los Alamos National Laboratory and the IEEE PES General Meeting, and to give keynote addresses at international conferences, including IET APSCOM, IFAC CPES, SmartGridComm, MICNON, MTNS and PSCC on aspects of power grids and system theory. He has several editorial roles including: an Editor for the Springer Book Series on Power Electronics and Power Systems; on the Editorial Board for the journals Sustainable Energy, Grids and Networks (SEGAN), the International Journal of Electrical Power and Energy Systems (IJEPES), Foundations and Trends in Electric Energy Systems and Journal of Control and Decision (China). He has several other advisory editor roles.
    </string>
    <string name="teinfo12">
    Dr. Y. Hou\n\nAssociate Professor\n\nB.Sc.(Eng), Ph.D.\nEmail: yhhou@eee.hku.hk\nWeb: https://www.eee.hku.hk/~yhhou\nTel.: 2857-8489\nOffice: CB 508\n\nResearch Interests\n\nElectric Power Systems Analysis; Self-healing smart grid construction; Integration of Renewable Energy Sources; Power System Resource Planning; Electricity Market Theory; Complex network and systems theory; Artificial Intelligence\n\nDr. Yunhe Hou received his B.Sc. (Eng) and Ph.D. degrees in Electrical Engineering all from Huazhong University of Science and Technology, China in 1999 and 2005, respectively.\n\nBefore joining the University of Hong Kong in 2009, he served as a researcher with University College Dublin, National University of Ireland, Dublin, Ireland, from September 2008 to July 2009. From March 2008 to August 2008, he was a postdoctoral researcher at Iowa State University, U.S.A. He also worked as a postdoctoral research fellow at Tsinghua University, China, from September 2005 to August 2007. In 2010, he was a visiting scientist with Laboratory for Information and Decision Systems, Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT), Cambridge, MA, USA
    </string>

    <string name="teinfo13">
    Dr. K.B. Huang\n\nAssistant Professor\n\nB.Eng., M.Eng. (National University of Singapore), Ph.D. (UT Austin).\nEmail: huangkb@eee.hku.hk\nWeb: https://www.eee.hku.hk/~wirelesslab/\nTel.: 2859 8026\nOffice: CB 611\n\nResearch Interests\n\nMachine Learning and Wireless Communications\nEdge Learning\nMobile Edge Computing\nWireless Power Transfer\nMIMO communications\n\nBiography\n\n\Kaibin Huang received the B.Eng. (first-class hons.) and the M.Eng. from the National University of Singapore, respectively, and the Ph.D. degree from The University of Texas at Austin (UT Austin), all in electrical engineering. Since Jan. 2014, he has been an assistant professor in the Dept. of Electrical and Electronic Engineering (EEE) at The University of Hong Kong. He is an adjunct professor in the School of EEE at Yonsei University in S. Korea. He used to be a faculty member in the Dept. of EEE at Yonsei University. His research interests focus on the analysis and design of wireless networks using stochastic geometry and multi-antenna techniques.\n\nHe frequently serves on the technical program committees of major IEEE conferences in wireless communications. He has been the technical chair/co-chair for the IEEE CTW 2013, the Comm. Theory Symp. of IEEE GLOBECOM 2014, and the Adv. Topics in Wireless Comm. Symp. of IEEE/CIC ICCC 2014 and has been the track chair/co-chair for IEEE PIMRC 2015, IEE VTC Spring 2013, Asilomar 2011 and IEEE WCNC 2011. Currently, he is an editor for IEEE Journal on Selected Areas in Communications (JSAC) series on Green Communications and Networking, IEEE Transactions on Wireless Communications, IEEE Wireless Communications Letters. He was also a guest editor for the JSAC special issues on communications powered by energy harvesting and an editor for IEEE/KICS Journal of Communication and Networks (2009-2015). He is an elected member of the SPCOM Technical Committee of the IEEE Signal Processing Society. Dr. Huang received the 2015 IEEE ComSoc Asia Pacific Outstanding Paper Award, Outstanding Teaching Award from Yonsei, Motorola Partnerships in Research Grant, the University Continuing Fellowship from UT Austin, and a Best Paper Award from IEEE GLOBECOM 2006.
    </string>

    <string name="teinfo14">
    Prof. R.S.Y. Hui\n\nChair of Power Electronics\n\nPhilip K H Wong Wilson K L Wong\nProfessorship in Electrical Engineering\nB.Sc (Eng.) Birmingham, Ph.D. (Imperial College), D.I.C., FIEEE, FIET, FIEAust, FTSE (Aust. Academy of Tech. Sci. &amp; Eng.), FREng (Royal Academy of Engineering, U.K.)\nEmail:ronhui@eee.hku.hk\nTel.: 2859 2706\nOffice: CB 601E\n\nResearch Interests\n\nPower Electronics – electric power conversion, planar coreless transformer technology, wireless power transfer, sustainable lighting technology, renewable energy technologies and smart grid technolog\n\“Discoveries come from the resonance of human minds and the creation. It is important to know the Creator. So do read the Bible.\n\Professor Ron Hui received his BSc (Eng) Hons at the University of Birmingham in 1984 and a D.I.C. and PhD at Imperial College London in 1987. He was a Lecturer at the University of Nottingham, UK in 1987–90. In 1990, he joined the University of Technology, Sydney, and was appointed Senior Lecturer at the University of Sydney, in 1992, where he became a Reader in 1995. He joined the City University of Hong Kong (CityU) as a Professor in 1996 and was promoted to Chair Professor in 1998. In 2001–04, he served as an Associate Dean of the Faculty of Science and Engineering at CityU. From July 2011, he holds the Chair Professorship at the University of Hong Kong and Imperial College London\n\He has published over 400 technical papers, including more than 230 refereed journal publications and 10 book chapters. Over 60 of his patents have been adopted by industry. He is a Fellow of the IEEE (2003) and IET (1996). Since 2013, he has been the Editor of the Journal on Selected and Emerging Topics in Power Electronics. He has been an Associate Editor of the IEEE Transactions on Power Electronics since 1997 and an Associate Editor of the IEEE Transactions on Industrial Electronics since 2007. He has been appointed twice as an IEEE Distinguished Lecturer by the IEEE Power Electronics Society in 2004 and 2006. He served as one of the 18 Administrative Committee members of the IEEE Power Electronics Society and was the Chairman of its Constitution and Bylaws Committee from 2002-2010. He received the Excellent Teaching Award at CityU in 1998 and the Earth Champion Award in 2008. He won an IEEE Best Paper Award from the IEEE IAS Committee on Production and Applications of Light in 2002, and four 1st-Place IEEE Power Electronics Transactions Prize Paper Awards (2009, 2010, 2014, 2015). His inventions on wireless charging platform technology underpin key dimensions of Qi, the world’s first wireless power standard launched by the Wireless Power Consortium in 2010, with freedom of positioning and localized charging features for wireless charging of consumer electronics. The Wireless Power Consortium now comprises over 210 companies worldwide. He also pioneered the Photo-Electro-Thermal Theory for LED Systems, unifying the nonlinear interactions of heat, light, power and color under the same mathematical framework\n\In Nov. 2010, he received the IEEE Rudolf Chope R&amp;D Award from the IEEE Industrial Electronics Society, the IET Achievement Medal (The Crompton Medal) and was elected to the Fellowship of the Australian Academy of Technological Sciences &amp; Engineering. In 2016, he was elected as a Fellow of the Royal Academy of Engineering, U.K.
    </string>

    <string name="teinfo15">
    Dr. L. Jiang\n\nAssociate Professor\n\nB.E. BUAA; M.E. Tsinghua; Ph.D, UIUC.\nEmail:ljiang@eee.hku.hk\nTel.: 2857-8484\nOffice: CB 515\n\nResearch Interests\n\nResearch Focuses: \nLarge-scale heterogeneous electromagnetics, VLSI power integrity and signal integrity, nano-scale electromagnetism for THz and optoelectronics, and microwave material engineering inspired by nano optics.\n\nBrief Bio:\nDr. Lijun Jiang received the Bachelor Degree in electrical engineering from the Beijing University of Aeronautics and Astronautics in 1993, the Master Degree from the Tsinghua University in 1996, and the Ph.D from the University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign (UIUC) in 2004. From 1996 to 1999, he was an Application Engineer with the Hewlett-Packard Company (HP). From 2004 to 2009, he has been the Postdoc, the Research Staff Member, and the Senior Engineer at IBM T.J. Watson Research Center. Since Dec. 2009, he has been the Associate Professor at the Department of Electrical and Electronic Engineering, the University of Hong Kong. He was the Senior Visiting Professor at Tsinghua University from Jun. 2013 to Jun. 2014. And he has been the visiting scholar to Professor T. Itoh’s group at UCLA since Sept. 2014 and spent his Sabbatical at UCLA during Sept. 2014 to Mar. 2015.\n\nAwards:\nHe and his research team have received numerous international awards and recognitions for outstanding researches he mentored and conducted.\n\nYoung Scientist Award, PIERS 2018, Toyama, Japan, Aug. 2018. (Advisor of the awardee)\n Best Student Paper Award 3rd Prize, PIERS 2018, Toyama, Japan, Aug. 2018. (Advisor of the student)\n Young Scientist Award, 2018 International Applied Computational Electromagnetics Society Symposium in China (ACES-China 2018), Beijing, China, Jul. 2018. (Advisor of the awardee)\n Outstanding Student Paper Award, the Cross Strait Quad-Regional Radio Science and Wireless Technology Conference (CSQRWC) 2018, Xuzhou, China, Jul. 2018. (Advisor of the student)\n Challenge Cup National Competition – Hong Kong Regional Final: Hong Kong University Student Innovation and Entrepreneurship Competition 2018 Second Prize Award. (Advisor of the awardee)\n Technical Achievement Award by IEEE EMC Society, Singapore, May 2018.\n Outstanding Young Scientist Award by IEEE APEMC, Singapore, May 2018. (Advisor of the awardee)\n The Third Place Best Student Paper Award, International Applied Computational Electromagnetics (ACES) Symposium, Firenze, Italy, Mar. 2017.\n The Best Poster Paper Award, IEEE EPEPS, San Diego, CA, Oct. 2016.\n The Best Student Paper Award, 2nd Runner-Up, the 17th IEEE Macau/HK AP/MTT Postgraduate Conference, Macau, Oct., 2016.\n 2016 President’s Memorial Award Presented in Memory of Guy deBurgh and Bill Kimmel, IEEE Int. Symposium on EMC, Ottawa, Canada, Jul. 2016.\n 2016 Best Student Symposium Paper Award First Place, IEEE Int. Symposium on EMC, Ottawa, Canada, Jul. 2016.\n EMTS 2016 Young Scientist Award, URSI Commission B International Symposium on Electromagnetic Theory (EMTS 2016) in Espoo, Finland on Aug. 2016.\n Honorable Mention EMTS 2016 Young Scientist Best Paper, URSI Commission B International Symposium on Electromagnetic Theory (EMTS 2016) in Espoo, Finland on Aug. 2016.\n Honorable Mention of 2015 IEEE AP-S Student Paper Competition, Jul. 2015.\n The 23th IEEE EPEP Best Paper Award, Portland, Oregon, Oct. 2014.\n The Best Student Paper Award (2nd Place) in Antennas and Microwave Engineering at 2014 PIERS, Guangzhou, Aug. 2014.\n The Student Paper Award at the 12th International Workshop on Finite Elements for Microwave Engineering, Chengdu, China, May. 2014.\n The First Place Best Student Paper Award of 30th International Review of Progress in Applied Computational Electromagnetics (ACES), Jacksonville, FL, Mar. 2014.\n The Finalist of the Best Student Paper Award at IEEE International EMC Symposium, 2014.\n The First Place of the Best Student Paper Award of IEEE 14th HK AP/MTT Postgraduate Conference, 2013.\n The Finalist of IEEE/ACM ICCAD Best Paper Award, San Jose, CA, 2012.\n IBM Research Technical Achievement Award, IBM T. J. Watson Research, USA, 2008.\n IBM First Patent Application Invention Achievement Award, IBM T. J. Watson Research, USA, 2007.\n T. Lo Outstanding Research Award, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign, USA, 2004.\n IEEE Microwave Theory and Techniques Society Graduate Fellowship Award, USA, 2003.\n National Collegiate Engineering Awards (NCAA), the United States Achievement, USA, 2001.\n Hewlett-Packard (HP) STAR Award, Hewlett Packard Headquarter, USA, 1998.\n Best Paper Winner of the 1st Chinese GPS Technology Symposium, China, 1994.\n\nScholarships:\nHe is an IEEE Senior Member, the Associate Editor of IEEE Transactions on Antennas and Propagation, the Associate Editor of Progress in Electromagnetics Research, the Associate Editor of ACES Express, the Associate Guest Editor of the Proceedings of IEEE Special Issue in 2011~2012, an IEEE AP-S Member, an IEEE MTT-S member, an IEEE EMC-S member, an ACES member, and a member of Chinese Computational Electromagnetics Society. He was the Semiconductor Research Cooperation (SRC) Industrial Liaison for several academic projects. He served as the Scientific Consultant to Hong Kong ASTRI (Hong Kong Applied Science and Technology Research Institute Company Limited) in 2010-2011, the Panelist of the Expert Review Panel (ERP) of Hong Kong R&amp;D Centre for Logistics and Supply Chain Management Enabling Technologies since Jan. 1st, 2013.\n\nAcademic Services:\nHe is the TPC Chair of 2016 IEEE APEMC, the TPC Chair of the 7th International Conference on Nanophotonics (ICNP)/the 3rd Conference on Advances in Optoelectronics and Micro/Nano Optics (AOM), the General co-chair of 2013 International Workshop on Pulsed Electromagnetic Field at Delft, the Netherlands, the TPC Co-chair of the 12th International Workshop on Finite Elements for Microwave Engineering, the PIERS SC1 Co-chair since 2014, the General Chair of 2014 IEEE 14th HK AP/MTT Postgraduate Conference. He was the elected TPC member of IEEE EPEP since 2014, the TPC member of IEEE EDAPS since 2010, the TPC member of 2013 IEEE ICMTCE, the scientific committee member of 2010 IEEE SMEE, the special session organizers of IEEE EDAPS, IEEE EMC, ACES, AP-RASC, co-organizer of HKU Computational Science and Engineering Workshops in 2010-2012, the TC-9 and TC-10 member of IEEE EMC-S since 2011, and session chairs of many international conferences. He also serves as the reviewer of IEEE Transactions on several topics, and other primary electromagnetics and microwave related journals. He has been working collaboratively with frontier international researchers.
    </string>
    <string name="teinfo16">
    Prof. R.Y.K. Kwok\n\nProfessor\nAssociate Vice-President (Teaching and Learning)\nB.Sc. HKU; M.Phil., Ph.D. HKUST; SMACM, FHKIE, FIEEE, FIET\nEmail: Ricky.Kwok@hku.hk\nWeb: https://www.eee.hku.hk/~ykwok\nTel.: 2859-8059\nOffice: CB 604\n\nResearch Interests\n\nParallel and Distributed Systems; Wireless Networkin\n\Prof. Kwok (Ricky) received a B.Sc. degree in Computer Engineering from the University of Hong Kong in 1991, and the M.Phil. and Ph.D. degrees, both in Computer Science, from the Hong Kong University of Science and Technology (HKUST) in 1994 and 1997, respectively. Before returning to the University of Hong Kong as an Assistant Professor in August 1998, he was a Visiting Scholar for one year in the Parallel Processing Laboratory, the School of Electrical and Computer Engineering at Purdue University (West Lafayette, Indiana, USA), where he worked on a DARPA research project in the field of distributed heterogeneous computing. During his sabbatical leave year (from August 2004 to July 2005), Ricky worked as a Visiting Associate Professor in the Internet and Grid Computing Laboratory, Department of Electrical Engineering–Systems at the University of Southern California (Los Angeles, California, USA), where he conducted research on several interesting Internet security problems such as DDoS defense and traceback, worm containment and signature generation, etc. From July 2007 to May 2009, he also worked as an Associate Professor in the Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering at the Colorado State University (Fort Collins, Colorado, USA), where he taught courses and conducted research in the areas of wireless sensor networks, high performance computer architecture, reconfigurable computing systems, and heterogeneous computing\n\Ricky’s research focus has been on designing efficient communication protocols and robust resources management algorithms toward enabling large scale distributed mobile computing. In these research areas, he has authored one textbook, co-authored another two textbooks, and published more than 200 technical papers in various leading journals, research books, and refereed international conference proceedings. He is a Senior member of the Association for Computing Machinery (ACM). Ricky is a Fellow of the HKIE, the IEEE, and the IET. He is also a member of the IEEE Computer Society and the IEEE Communications Society. From March 2006 to December 2011, Ricky served on the Editorial Board of the Journal of Parallel and Distributed Computing as a Subject Area Editor in Peer-to-Peer Computing. Since January 2013, Ricky has been an Associate Editor for the IEEE Transactions on Parallel and Distributed Systems\n\Ricky has been actively involved in various administrative tasks at the departmental, school, and university levels. He served as the Co-Director of the Computer Engineering Programme from 2000 to 2002. He then served as the Programme Director of the Master of Science in Electrical and Electronic Engineering programme from 2002 to 2007. Since 2002, he has also been serving as the Associate Programme Director of the Master of Science in Electronic Commerce and Internet Computing programme. He was the Director of the High Performance Computing Laboratory from 2000 to 2007. He was also elected to serve on the Head’s Advisory Committee (HAC) from 2000 to 2007. During 2010 to 2014, Ricky was the Chairman of the Departmental Curriculum Review and Development Committee (DCRDC), managing curriculum reform for smooth transition to four-year degree programmes. From 2012 to 2014, he was the Deputy Head of the Department, overseeing resources management issues. Ricky is currently Associate Vice-President (Teaching and Learning), assisting the Vice-President and Pro-Vice-Chancellor (Teaching and Learning) in various T&amp;L endeavors related to e-learning (e.g., MOOCs). Check here about the exciting T&amp;L activities at HKU. As of April 2015, he also serves as an Associate Dean of Engineering, looking after special projects and other new initiatives\n\Ricky received the Outstanding Young Researcher Award from HKU in November 2004. In January 2010, one of his journal papers was ranked #4 among top ten All-Time Most Cited Papers published in the IEEE Transactions on Parallel and Distributed Systems, based on Scopus and Google Scholar citation counts as of October 2009 (see the Editor’s Note for details). In April 2013, he got the Outstanding Reviewer Service Award from the IEEE Computer Society (under the Reviewer Appreciation Program) because as of 2013 he was the All-Time Most Prolific Reviewer for the IEEE Transactions on Parallel and Distributed Systems (see this official announcement)\n\Google Scholar Profile\ResearcherID Profile
    </string>
    <string name="teinfo17">
    Prof. P.T. Lai\n\nProfessor\n\nB.Sc. (Eng.), Ph.D. H.K.; M.I.E.E.E.\nEmail:laip@eee.hku.hk\nTel.: 2859-2691\nOffice: CB 505\n\nResearch Interests\n\nSemiconductor processing; Device physics, modeling and simulation; Integrated sensors. Prof. Lai’s Ph.D. research at the University of Hong Kong was related to the design of small-sized MOS transistor with emphasis on narrow-channel effects. The work involved the development of both analytical and numerical models. Worked as a Post-doctoral fellow : i) proposed and implemented a novel self-aligned structure for bipolar transistor, ii) designed and implemented an advanced poly-emitter bipolar process with emphasis on self-alignment and trench isolation. His current research interests are on thin gate dielectrics for Metal-Oxide-Semiconductor Field-Effect Transistor (MOSFET) based on Si, SiC, GaN, Ge, organics, and on microsensors for detecting gases, heat, light, and flow.
    </string>
    <string name="teinfo18">
    Prof. E.Y.M. Lam\n\nProfessor\nAssociate Dean of Engineering\n\nB.S., M.S., Ph.D. Stanford University\nEmail:elam@eee.hku.hk\nWeb: https://www.eee.hku.hk/~elam/\nTel.: 2241-5942\nOffice: CB 504\n\nResearch Interests\n\nComputational optics and imaging algorithms; Digital image processing; Biomedical optics; Computational lithography and semiconductor inspection; Machine learning and computational science; Pattern recognition, classification, and analysis; Technology for teaching and learning. Prof. Edmund Lam received the B.S. degree (with distinction) in 1995, the M.S. degree in 1996, and the Ph.D. degree in 2000, all in electrical engineering from Stanford University. He is now a Professor in Electrical and Electronic Engineering and the Director of the Computer Engineering program at The University of Hong Kong. He has broad research interests around the theme of computational optics and imaging, from the design of efficient imaging algorithms to the processing of the massive image data for various applications. For his research, he has been presented the HKU Outstanding Young Researcher Award and the IBM Faculty Award. He is also a Fellow of the Optical Society (OSA), the Society of Photo-optical Instrumentation Engineers (SPIE), as well as the Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers (IEEE). With regards to teaching, he has taught at all levels of the departmental courses, and devoted considerable efforts in reshaping the first course in the electrical and electronic engineering curriculum. He was given an engineering Best Teacher Award, and the university-wide Outstanding Teaching Award (team award). Earlier, he had also been invited to teach at the Department of Electrical Engineering and Computer Science at Massachusetts Institute of Technology as a Visiting Associate Professor.
    </string>
    <string name="teinfo19">
    Dr. J.C.K. Lam\n\nAssociate Professor\n\nBA, MA, MSc, PhD (Env. Policy); HK.\nEmail: jacquelinelam@hku.hk\nTel.: 2219 4843\nOffice: CB 717\n\nResearch Interests\n\n… God said, “Let us make mankind in our image, in our likeness, so that they may rule over the fish in the sea and the birds in the sky, over the livestock and all the wild animals, and over all the creatures that move along the ground.”  [Genesis 1:26-27]\n\nDr. Jacqueline Lam obtained her PhD in Environmental Policy from the Centre of Urban Planning in Environmental Management, Faculty of Architecture, the University of Hong Kong in 2008. Her PhD study investigates theoretically appealing but practically inconclusive debates over the positive relation between superior environmental performance and company competitiveness with a focus on the public transport sector in Hong Kong and California. Her study examined how the design and implementation of environmental regulation can affect the relationship.\n\nHer major research areas include low-carbon/clean energy and environment policy and behavioural study from an interdisciplinary perspective. Interdisciplinary research has increasingly been emphasized to tackle the highly complex and multi-faceted topic of clean energy and environment. Dr. Lam’s research philosophy is INTEGRATION, inspired by the effective and meaningful connection and complementation of different body parts. If God wills, she wants to demonstrate that such an approach is both necessary and fruitful in environmental studies. Her research is strongly driven by the conviction that clean energy and environmental policies should be carefully guided by scientific evidence, as well as expert-led, socially inclusive participatory processes.\n\nThe specific topics Dr. Lam has been working on are: (1) conditions that govern the process of clean energy transitions in the society and the approaches for managing these transitions, (2) policies and strategies that can effectively stimulate the process of socio-technological change and their relative potentials, and (3) ways to engage the society and build trust for more effective energy governance. She has close connections with the industry, government and the society. The work carries a strong element of university-industry collaboration, community education and outreach.\n\nDr. Lam is the recipient of the 2012-13 university-wide Research Assistant Professorship, and also a core member of the open innovation network, Initiative on Clean Energy and Environment. Prior to joining the Department (2008-12), she was a teaching consultant and postdoctoral fellow of the Kadoorie Institute in HKU.\n\nIn 2012, in collaboration with a group of scientists and engineers, she won a $3.2 million RGC-SPPR grant to conduct a 4-year interdisciplinary public policy research project titled “Effective Nuclear Safety Governance for Hong Kong and Guangdong China: A Stakeholder Trust-based Model”. She was the Associate Editor of International Journal of Technology, Knowledge and Society (special issue) in 2011-12. She was a member of the Admission Committee for MSc in Environmental Management (2008, 2010-2012) She taught two master courses Environmental Policy (2007-12) and Principles of Sustainable Development (2008-10), supervises MSc thesis for MSc in Environmental Management (2008-13) and will teach Sustainability and Climate Change (ELEC7407) for MSc in Electronic Engineering (2013-14).\n\n

    Awarded Research Grants\n\n2012 – 15\nLead Co-Investigator, Research Grants Council- Public Policy Research Fund (Amount funded: $840,000)\nAnalyzing Stakeholders’ Views on Environmental Issues through Text Analysis — An Interdisciplinary Approach Using Computational Content Analysis (with Prof. YL Cheung (CUHK), Principal Investigator, Prof. WK Chan (CUHK); Prof. Richard Walker (CityU) and Prof. Peter Hills (HKU))\n\n2012 – 15\nLead Co-Investigator, Research Grants Council- Strategic Public Policy Research Fund (Amount funded: $3,200,000)\nEffective Nuclear Safety Governance for Hong Kong and Guangdong China: A Stakeholder Trust-based Model  (with Prof. Dennis Y.C. Leung, Project Coordinator, and other academics spanning across five disciplinary units, including engineering and medicine; and Principal Advisor Prof. V.O.K. Li)\n\n2011 – 12\nLead Co-Investigator, Research Grants Council- Public Policy Research Fund (Amount funded: $570,000)\nManaging the Transition towards the Low-carbon Economy: Stakeholder Engagement for Technological Environmental Innovation Decision-making in Hong Kong (with Prof. Victor OK Li, Principal Investigator, Prof. Peter Hills and Daphne NY Mah, Co-investigators)\n\nPrincipal Investigator, HKU-University Development Fund-ICEE (Amount funded: $280,000)\nAn Investigation of the HKU-ICEE Open-innovation Network on Knowledge Discovery and Exchange (with Prof. Peter Hills, Co-Investigator, and others)\n\nPrincipal Investigator, HKU-University Development Fund-ICEE (Amount funded: $250,000)\nAn Evaluation of the Policy Effectiveness of Renewable Energy Technologies in Hong Kong, Asia, Europe and USA (with Prof. Richard Walker and Prof. Peter Hills, Co-Investigators)\n\nLead Co-Investigator &amp; Project Leader, Environment &amp; Conservation Fund-EE&amp;CA (Amount funded: $232,000)\nA Persuasive Technology Approach to Promoting Low-Carbon Footprint Food in the HKU Community (with Prof. Peter Hills, Principal Investigator, and other disciplinary units in HKU)\n\n2009\nPrincipal Investigator, HKU-Small Project Funding (Amount funded: $45,000) Open Innovation, Corporate Response to Climate Change and Sustainability, and Competitive Advantage (with Prof. Peter Hills, Supervisor)\n\n2004\nLead Co-Investigator, CLP Power Renewable Energy Fund (Amount funded: $80,000) A Feasibility Study of Fuel Cell Application on Public Buses in Hong Kong (with Prof. Peter Hills, Principal Investigator, and H.T. Leung and H.Y. Wong, team members)
    </string>
    <string name="teinfo20">
    Dr. K.H. Lam\n\nLecturer\n\nPh.D.\nEmail:khlam@eee.hku.hk\nTel.: 2857-8401\nOffice: CB 609\n\nResearch Interests\n\nDr. Sam K.H. LAM received his bachelor degree in Electrical &amp; Electronic Engineering from the University of Hong Kong in 1994. He worked in the Building Services industry after graduation and then returned to the Alma Mater for joining the HKU Photovoltaic research team in 1998. He participated in many pioneer works on promoting the application of Photovoltaic systems in Hong Kong. He was one of the founding members and subsequently elected the Chairman (2008-2009) of the Hong Kong Photovoltaic Consortium. He was also a member of the task group led by EMSD for drafting the Technical Guidelines on Grid Connection of Renewable Energy Power Systems. In 2007, he received his Ph D in Architecture from The University of Hong Kong and then started working in the Photovoltaic industry. In May 2014, he was appointed as Lecturer at the University of Hong Kong\n\Last updated: May 6th, 2015
    </string>
    <string name="teinfo21">
    Dr. W.H. Lam\n\nAssistant Professor\n\nB.Sc. Essex; M.Sc., DIC Lond.; Ph.D. Southampton; C.Eng., M.I.E.T., M.H.K.I.E., S.M.I.E.E.E.\nEmail:whlam@eee.hku.hkTel.: 2859-1912\nOffice: CB 715\n\nResearch Interests\n\nDigital mobile radio communications systems, spread spectrum communications systems and Intelligent Transport Systems (ITS) Having obtained the BSc and the MSc from Essex University and Imperial College (UK) respectively, Dr. Lam received the Ph.D. degree (with SERC CASE award) from the University of Southampton, U.K., where he was sponsored by and collaborated with British Telecom Research Laboratory (BTRL), Plessey Research Laboratory (UK) and Bell Lab (US) to work on the pan-European digital cellular mobile radio communications systems which is then known as GSM . He was a member of the Mobile Radio Research Group and specialized in digital cellular mobile radio communications including GSM, CDMA and RACE. In 1988, he joined STL (STC Laboratory) in Harlow, U.K., where was responsible for the UK DTI-LINK project ” phones on the move ” of DTI, micro-cellular project, the formulation of the personal communication systems (PCN) architecture and subsequently winning the operation license application of the British PCN. In 1989, he was with Pan-European Digital Cellular Infrastructure R &amp; D center of Motorola Limited, Swindon, U.K. , where he was responsible for the development and validation of the GSM systems, radio resource network management project which encompassed radio propagation measurements and prediction, Geographical Information Systems (GIS), GSM &amp; PCN radio frequency planning and radio network planning. In 1991, Dr. Lam joined the University of Hong Kong where he is currently heading a group of researchers in the field of mobile radio communications and intelligent transport systems (ITS). He has been very active locally and internationally, and has published more than 63 technical publications in the field of digital cellular mobile radio communications. He was the chairman and organizer of a series of regional conferences on mobile radio communications and a distinguished speaker and chairperson at several international conferences &amp; meetings. Dr. Lam had more than 15-year R &amp; D experience in digital cellular mobile radio communications. His current research interests are pico-cellular/indoor personal communications networks (PCN), UMTS, FLMTS, and Mobile CDMA, radio propagation, radio resource optimization, wireless LAN and WAN, broadband ISDN, Global Positioning System (GPS) and Intelligent Transport Systems (ITS).

    </string>
    <string name="teinfo22">
    Dr. C.K. Lee\n\nAssociate Professor\n\nB.Eng, Ph.D. City University of Hong Kong\nEmail:cklee@eee.hku.hk\nTel.: 2859-2705\nOffice: CB 610\n\nResearch Interests\n\nPower Electronics; Smart Grid Technology; Wireless Power Transfer Technology; Planar Electromagnetics Desig\n\Dr. Chi Kwan Lee received the BEng and Ph.D. Degrees in electronic engineering from the City University of Hong Kong (CityU) in 1999 and 2004, respectively. After graduation, he joined the Power Electronics Research Centre at the National University of Ireland, Galway as a Post-doctoral Research Fellow researching into solar power and battery management system. Afterwards, He was employed by a power electronics company as a Senior Engineer. During that time, He was invited to take part in the R&amp;D project at the Delta Electronics Research Centre to design and develop the reactive power controller. He then worked at the Research Centre for Power Electronics in the CityU from 2006-08. In 2008, he joined the Hong Kong Polytechnic University as a Lecturer. He was invited by Imperial College London to be a Visiting Academic for the International Smart-Grid Research Program in summer 2010 and 2011. He joined the department as an Assistant Professor in 2012. Dr Lee is author or coauthor of over 30 journal and conference papers. He is the co-inventor of 1 U.S. patent. He won the championship of the Institution of Electrical Engineers (IEE) Hong Kong Younger Members Section Project Competition in 1999. Nationally, he received the merit for his project in the 6th Challenger Cup Competition of Science &amp; Technology. He was awarded full scholarships for his postgraduate study. He is a member of IEEE and serves as a reviewer for numerous journals including IEEE Transaction on Power Electronics, IEEE Transactions on Industrial Electronics and IEEE Transactions on Circuit and System, Part I.
    </string>

    <string name="teinfo23">
    Ir W.K. Lee\n\nPrincipal Lecturer\n\nEmail:wklee@eee.hku.hk\nTel.: 2857-8403\nOffice: CB 605\n\nLast updated: May 7th, 2015
    </string>

    <string name="teinfo24">
    Dr. W.N. Lee\n\nAssociate Professor\n\nPh.D., M.Phil., M.S., B.S.\nEmail:wnlee@eee.hku.hk\nWeb: https://www.eee.hku.hk/~wnlee\nTel.: 2859-2703\nOffice: CB 520\n\nResearch Interests\n\nNovel medical ultrasound techniques, such as ultrafast ultrasound imaging, strain imaging and shear wave imaging, particularly for cardiovascular applications; Biomedical imaging; Image processing.\n\nWei-Ning Lee received her B.S. and M.S. degrees in electrical engineering from National Taiwan University (Taipei, Taiwan) and her Ph.D. degree in biomedical engineering from Columbia University (New York, NY, USA). Dr. Lee then pursued her postdoctoral training at Institut Langevin in ESPCI ParisTech (Paris, France), where she carried out a pioneer work on mapping myocardial fibers by ultrasound elastic tensor imaging. Dr. Lee joined the Department of Electrical and Electronic Engineering, and the Medical Engineering Program, at the University of Hong Kong as an Assistant Professor in September in 2012. Her main research interests include novel medical ultrasound techniques—ultrafast ultrasound imaging, strain imaging and shear wave imaging, imaging and mechanics of cardiovascular and musculoskeletal systems, and image processing. She is a member of the IEEE Ultrasonics, Ferroelectrics, and Frequency Control Society, is currently an Academic Editor of PLOS ONE, and serves on the International Advisory Board of Physics in Medicine and Biology. She received the New Investigator Award at the American Institute of Ultrasound in Medicine (AIUM) Annual Convention in 2009 an Early Career Award from 2013/14 Hong Kong Research Grants Council.
    </string>

    <string name="teinfo25">
        Dr. K.C. Leung\n\nAssistant Professor\n\nB.Eng. HKUST; M.Sc., Ph.D. USC; M.I.E.E.E.\nEmail:kcleung@eee.hku.hk\nTel.: 2857-8481\nOffice: CB 518\nResearch Interests\n\nCommuication networks; vehicle-to-grid (V2G); smart city; Internet Protocol technologies; wireless packet scheduling; mathematics education.\n\nB.Eng. (First Class Honors), Computer Science, HKUST, November 1994\nM.Sc., Electrical Engineering (Computer Networks), USC, December 1997\nPh.D., Computer Engineering, USC, December 2000\n\nDr. Leung received the B.Eng. degree in Computer Science from the Hong Kong University of Science and Technology (HKUST), Hong Kong, in 1994, the M.Sc. degree in Electrical Engineering (Computer Networks) and the Ph.D. degree in Computer Engineering from the University of Southern California (USC), Los Angeles, CA, USA, in 1997 and 2000, respectively. He was a member of the team that won the Fourth ACM (Hong Kong Chapter) Scholastic Programming Contest, Hong Kong, in July 1994. He participated as an alternate team member to the 1994-1995 19th Annual International Collegiate Programming Contest (Contest Finals), Nashville, TN, USA, in March 1995. He worked as Senior Research Engineer at Nokia Research Center, Nokia Inc., Irving, TX, USA during 2001 and 2002, and was involved in the design, standardization, and implementation of a signalling payload compression protocol architecture used in wireless networks. He was Assistant Professor in the Department of Computer Science at Texas Tech University, Lubbock, TX, USA between 2002 and 2005. Currently, he is Assistant Professor in the Department of Electrical and Electronic Engineering at the University of Hong Kong (HKU), Hong Kong.\n\nFor information about the family of my research students, please click here.
    </string>
    <string name="teinfo26">
    Dr. K.H. Li\n\nResearch Assistant Professor\n\nB.Eng., Ph.D\nEmail:khli@eee.hku.hk\nTel.: 2857 8495\nOffice: CB 521\nResearch Interests\n\nIII-V based materials and optoelectronic devices, optical microcavities, semiconductor nanostructures, photonic system.\n\nDr. Kwai Hei Li received the B.Eng. and Ph.D. degrees in Electrical and Electronic Engineering from the University of Hong Kong in 2009 and 2013, respectively. After graduation, he received 1-year postdoctoral research training at the McGill University in Canada. He worked as a postdoctoral fellow in the Department of Electrical and Electronic Engineering at HKU from 2014 to 2016, where he is now a Research Assistant Professor. His main research interest is in fabrication and characterization of III-V semiconductor optical devices. He was the recipient of the Sir Edward Youde Memorial Fellowship for Postgraduate Research and the HKU Award for Outstanding Research Postgraduate Student 2012-2013. Dr. Li is a member of IEEE and serves as a reviewer for Applied Optics, Optics Express, Journal of Applied Physics, and Applied Physics Letters.
    </string>
    <string name="teinfo27">
    Prof. V.O.K. Li\n\nChair of Information Engineering\nCheng Yu-Tung Professorship in Sustainable development\n\nSB, SM, EE, ScD MIT; FHKEng, FIEEE, FIAE, FHKIE\nEmail:vli@eee.hku.hk\nTel.: 2857-8425\nOffice: CB 601D\n\nResearch Interests\n\nDevelopment and applications of information science (big data analytics and deep learning) to important societal problems, including clean energy and environment, internet of things, and smart city.\n\nS.B., Electrical Engg. and Computer Science, MIT, 1977\nS.M., Electrical Engg. and Computer Science, MIT, 1979\nEE, Electrical Engg. and Computer Science, MIT, 1980\nSc.D., Electrical Engg. and Computer Science, MIT, 1981\n\nVictor O.K. Li was born and raised in Hong Kong. He joined the University of Southern California (USC), Los Angeles, California, USA in February 1981, and became Professor of Electrical Engineering and Director of the USC Communication Sciences Institute. Since September 1997 he has been with the University of Hong Kong (HKU), Hong Kong, where he is Chair Professor of Information Engineering, Cheng Yu-Tung Professor in Sustainable Development, and Head of the Department of Electrical and Electronic Engineering. He served as Assoc. Dean of Engineering at HKU from 2007 to 2012. He has also served as Managing Director of Versitech Ltd. (http://www.versitech.hku.hk/), the technology transfer and commercial arm of HKU, and on the boards of Sunevison Holdings Ltd and China.com Ltd, listed on the Hong Kong Stock Exchange. He is very active in technology transfer. The co-author of seven US patents licensed for commercial exploitation, he also co-founded Accosys Ltd. with his PhD student. One of these patents, United States Patent No. US 6,543,053 B1, has been cited 343 times, and according to the Technology Transfer Office of HKU, is the most highly cited patent of HKU. He served as the Convenor of the Strategic Research Theme of Information Technology at HKU, and as Co-Director of the Area of Excellence in Information Technology funded by the Hong Kong government. He is the Chair of the Executive Committee, HKU Initiative on Clean Energy and Environment, an interdisciplinary research project with researchers from Engineering, Science, Architecture, and Social Science, and Director, HKU-Cambridge Clean Energy and Environment Research Platform. He is also a Member of the AsiaGlobal Fellows Faculty Committee of the Asian Global Institute. Sought by government, industry, and academic organizations, he has lectured and consulted extensively around the world. Prof. Li chaired the Computer Communications Technical Committee of the IEEE Communications Society 1987-1989, and the Los Angeles Chapter of the IEEE Information Theory Group 1983-1985. He co-founded the International Conference on Computer Communications and Networks (IC3N), and chaired its Steering Committee1992-1997. He also chaired various international workshops and conferences, including IEEE INFOCOM 2004 and IEEE PIMRC 2015. Prof. Li has served as an editor of IEEE Network, IEEE JSAC Wireless Communications Series, ACM/Springer Wireless Networks, IEEE Communications Surveys and Tutorials, Telecommunication Systems, and Springer Networking Science. He also guest edited special issues of IEEE JSAC, Computer Networks and ISDN Systems, and KICS/IEEE Journal of Communications and Networking. Prof. Li has been appointed to the Central Policy Unit and to the Hong Kong Information Infrastructure Advisory Committee by the Chief Executive of the Hong Kong Special Administrative Region (HKSAR). He has also served on various other HKSAR advisory committees, including the Innovation and Technology Fund (Electronics) Vetting Committee, the Small Entrepreneur Research Assistance Programme Committee, the Engineering Panel of the Research Grants Council, and the Task Force for the Hong Kong Academic and Research Network (HARNET) Development Fund of the University Grants Committee. He was a Distinguished Lecturer at the University of California at San Diego, at the University of London, at the National Science Council of Taiwan, and at the California Polytechnic Institute. Prof. Li has also delivered keynote speeches at many international conferences. He has received numerous awards, including the PRC Ministry of Education Changjiang Chair Professorship at Tsinghua University, the UK Royal Academy of Engineering Senior Visiting Fellowship in Communications, the Outstanding Researcher Award of HKU, the Outstanding Research Student Supervisor Award of HKU, the Croucher Foundation Senior Research Fellowship, and the Bronze Bauhinia Star, Government of HKSAR, China. He is a Fellow of the Hong Kong Academy of Engineering Sciences, the IEEE, the HKIE and the IAE.
    </string>
    <string name="teinfo28">
    Dr. T. Liu\n\nResearch Assistant Professor\n\nB.Sc. (Eng.), Ph.D.\nEmail:taoliu@eee.hku.hk\nTel.: 2219 4577\nOffice: CB 517\n\nResearch Interests\n\nPower system stability analysis, Complex dynamical networks, Distributed control, Event-triggered control, Switched systems.\n\nDr. Tao Liu received his B. Sc. (Eng.) degree from Northeastern University, China, in 2003 and his Ph.D. degree from the Australian National University, Australia, in 2011. He was a research fellow in the Research School of Engineering at the Australian National University from January to May 2012. During this period, he also held a visiting scholar position in the Centre of Excellence in Power Engineering at the University of Sydney, Australia. From June 2012 to August 2013, he worked as a post-doctoral fellow at the University of Groningen, the Netherlands. He also worked as a post-doctoral fellow at the University of Hong Kong from September 2013 to June 2015.
    </string>
    <string name="teinfo29">
    Dr. K.S. Lui\n\nAssociate Professor\n\nB. Eng., M.Phil. HKUST; Ph.D. UIUC\nEmail:kslui@eee.hku.hk\nWeb: www.eee.hku.hk/~kslui/\nTel.: 2859-7094\nOffice: CB 706\n\nResearch Interests\n\nNetwork Quality of Service issues; Topology aggregation; Network protocol design; Routing algorithm design\n\nDr. Lui obtained her BEng. (first class honor) and MPhil. degrees in computer science from the Hong Kong University of Science and Technology. She then received her PhD degree, also in computer science, from the University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign in 2002. Dr. Lui joins the department as an assistant professor in August 2002.
    </string>
    <string name="teinfo30">
    Dr. G.K.H. Pang\n\nAssociate Professor\n\nB.Sc. (Eng.) UK; Ph.D. Cambridge; C.Eng.; P.Eng.; M.I.E.T.; M.I.E.E.E.\nEmail:gpang@eee.hku.hk\nTel.: 2857-8492\nOffice: CB 509\n\nResearch Interests\n\nIntelligent control, fuzzy neural networks, intelligent transport systems, knowledge-based and algebraic approach to computer-aided control system design. Dr. Grantham K.H. Pang obtained his Ph.D. degree from the University of Cambridge in 1986. He was with the Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering, University of Waterloo, Canada, from 1986 to 1996 and joined the Department of Electrical and Electronic Engineering at The University of Hong Kong in 1996. Since 1988, he published more than 120 technical papers and has authored or co-authored six books. His research interests include machine vision for surface defect detection, optical communications, expert systems for control system design, intelligent control and intelligent transportation systems. He is in charge of the Industrial Automation Research Lab. Dr. Pang was the Organizing Chair of the 1996 IEEE Symposium on Computer-Aided Control System Design. Dr. Pang is an Editor of the International Journal of Intelligent Control and Systems, Machine Intelligence and Robotic Control, and Control and Computers. He is a Chartered Electrical Engineer, and a member of the IET, HKIE and IEEE. For more information, please see https://www.eee.hku.hk/~gpang/.
    </string>
    <string name="teinfo31">
    Ir Dr. M.H. Pong\n\nAssociate Professor\n\nB.Sc. Birmingham; Ph.D. Cambridge; C.Eng., M.I.E.T., Sen.M.I.E.E.E., M.H.K.I.E.\nEmail:mhp@eee.hku.hk\nTel.: 2859-7099\nOffice: CB 704\n\nResearch Interests\n\nSwitching power supplies and power electronics Dr. Bryan M.H.Pong graduated from Birmingham University with a 1st Class Hons. degree and he obtained his PhD degree from Cambridge University afterwards. He held several scholarships and prizes during this period. Later he received the Swan Premium from the Institution of Electrical Engineers (IEE, now IET). After graduation he joined National Semiconductor HK where he was a Senior Design Engineer and then Chief Design Engineer. Afterwards he joined ASTEC International where he was a Principal Engineer and later Division Engineering Manager. There he lead an Engineering Department to develop high frequency switching power supplies, battery chargers, and various power converters. Now he is an Associate Professor at the Hong Kong University. His research interest is Power Electronics &amp; Switching Power Supply. He is in charge of the Power Electronics Laboratory and the Electric Traction Laboratory in the Electrical &amp; Electronic Engineering Department. He is leading a team to carry out research on low voltage converter topologies, magnetic component design and Electromagnetic Interference (EMI) of switching power supplies. He focuses on applied research and started the “Switching Power Converter Development Program” which aimed to advance switching power converter technologies and foster cooperation with the industry. The Power Electronics Lab is now closely collaborating with many companies in the industry. Dr. Pong is a co-inventor of several US patents and has authored and co-authored a number of technical publications. Dr. Pong was a past chairman and a committee member of the Institute of Electronic &amp; Electrical Engineers Hong Kong Section (IEEE), PES/IAS/PELS Joint Chapter. He also served the Electrical Division of the Hong Kong Institution of Engineers.
    </string>
    <string name="teinfo32">
    Dr. P.W.T. Pong\n\nAssociate Professor\n\nB.ENG, The University of Hong Kong; Ph.D., University of Cambridge\nEmail:ppong@eee.hku.hkWeb: https://www.eee.hku.hk/~ppong\nTel.: 2857-8491\nOffice: CB 607\n\nResearch Interests\n\nSpintronics, Nanobiotechnology, and Smart Grid.\n\nPhilip W. T. Pong (Ph.D., FIET, FIMMM, FNS, CEng, CPhys, RPE, SMIEEE) is a chartered physicist, a chartered electrical engineer, a chartered energy engineer, and a registered professional engineer (Electrical, Electronics, Energy). He is working on magnetoresistive magnetic field sensors, smart grid, and nano-bio at the Department of Electrical and Electronic Engineering (EEE), HKU. He received a B.Eng. in EEE of HKU (1999-2002) with 1st class honours. Then he studied for a PhD in engineering from the University of Cambridge (2002-2005). After working as a postdoctoral researcher at the Magnetic Materials Group at the National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) for three years, he joined the HKU Faculty of Engineering where he is now an associate professor working on magnetic tunnel junction (MTJ) sensors, and the application of magnetoresistive sensors in smart grid and nanobiotechnology. He is a Fellow of the Institution of Engineering and Technology (FIET), a Fellow of the Institute of Materials, Minerals and Mining (FIMMM) and also a Fellow of the NANOSMAT Society (FNS). He is a Senior Member of IEEE and corporate member of HKIE in Electrical Division and Electronics Division. He is an associate editor for two SCI journals: International Journal of Modern Physics B and Modern Physics Letters B.
    </string>

    <string name="teinfo33">
      Dr. H.K.H. So\n\nAssociate Professor\n\nB.S., M.S., Ph.D.\nEmail:hso@eee.hku.hk\nWeb: https://www.eee.hku.hk/~hso\nTel.: 2859-2702\nOffice: CB 516\n\nResearch Interests\n\nReconfigurable Computing; FPGA Technology; Operating System Design for Reconfigurable Computers; Computer Architecture; Hardware/Software Codesign Methodology\n\Dr. Hayden Kwok-Hay So received his Ph.D., M.S., and B.S. degrees in Electrical Engineering and Computer Sciences all from the University of California, Berkeley in 2007, 2000 and 1998 respectively\n\Before joining the department in 2007, he was a member of the Berkeley Wireless Research Center where he developed BORPH, an operating system for the BEE2 FPGA platform. While working as an intern at Xilinx research lab, he developed a virtual file system for FPGA dynamic reconfiguration\n\His current research interests include integration methodologies between reconfigurable computers and conventional computers, reconfigurable computer architecture, application of reconfigurable computing technologies to high performance computing and high-end embedded systems, and reconfigurable computing education.
    </string>

    <string name="teinfo34">
    Prof. S.C. Tan\n\nProfessor,\nAssociate Head (UG and Student Affairs)\n\nB.Eng. (Hons.); M.Eng.; Ph.D.\nEmail:sctan@eee.hku.hk\nTel.: 2859-2707\nOffice: CB 719\n\nResearch Interests\n\nProf. Siew-Chong TAN is a tenured Full Professor at the University of Hong Kong, Hong Kong SAR. He received his B.Eng. (Honors) and M.Eng. degrees in Electrical Engineering from the National University of Singapore, Singapore, and Ph.D. in Electronic and Information Engineering, specializing in power electronics, from the Hong Kong Polytechnic University, Hong Kong SAR. He is Director of Emerging Power Electronics Laboratory and Director of 100 kVA Smart Grid Research Facility at the University of Hong Kong\n\TAN specializes in power electronics and control. He has published works in nonlinear and sliding mode control applications, LED drivers and lighting control, electric springs, resonant converters, and switched-capacitor converters. His research outputs, to date, include 2 research monographs, 2 book chapters, 101 journal papers, and 79 conference papers. He has obtained 16 patents for his work, with 3 pending patent applications. His recent awards include (1) Best Paper Award at IEEE ECCE 2016, (2) Outstanding Presentation Award at IEEE APEC 2016, (3) Best Student Poster Presentation Award at IEEE ECCE 2015, and (4) Second Prize Paper Award at IEEE PEDG 2014. His published works are listed in Google Scholar. He is one of the Top 1% Scholars (globally most-cited scientists according to Thomson Reuter’s Essential Science Indicators)\n\TAN is an active member of IEEE, serving as Associate Editor of IEEE TPEL and reviewer of many IEEE transactions and journals. He served as Organizing Committee Co-Chair for IEEE Workshop on Emerging Technologies: Wireless Power, Canada, 2018 and Technical Program Committee Co-Chair for IEEE International Conference on Smart Grid Communications, U.S.A., 2015. He had also served as technical committee member and review committee member in several international conferences. He is currently Member, Appeal Board Panel under Electricity Ordinance (Chapter 406), The Government of the Hong Kong Special Administrative Region. He is a practicing consultant and has worked on projects involving power outages, lithium battery testing, advisory role on LED patent litigations.
    </string>

    <string name="teinfo35">
    Prof. N.C. Tien\n\nChair Professor of Microsystems Technology\n\nEmail:nctien@hku.hk\nWeb: http://engg.hku.hk/home/dean.htm\nTel.: 2241 5394\nOffice: CB 612\n\nProfessor Norman C. Tien became the Dean of the Faculty of Engineering at the University of Hong Kong in June 2012. Previously, he served for five years as Dean and Nord Professor of Engineering at Case Western Reserve University’s Case School of Engineering in Cleveland, Ohio. He was also the Ohio Eminent Scholar in Condensed Matter Physics.\n\nDuring his tenure as Dean of the Case School of Engineering, Tien realized several key elements for his vision for the school with initiatives in energy and global outreach. He created the Great Lakes Institute for Energy Innovation to develop and advance sustainable energy generation through research, development, and education. The Institute also served as a vehicle to drive cultural change in the school by promoting multi-disciplinary, collaborative, large-scale research. In his mission to expand the school’s external presence, Tien began the San Diego-based Wireless Health Technology program, the school’s first office outside of Ohio. He also developed new collaborative partnerships with Chinese and Southeast Asian universities.\n\nTien’s research interests are in the area of micro and nanotechnology-including microelectromechanical (MEMS) systems-the fabrication of small structures, tools and instruments for use in wireless communications, biomedical systems and environmental monitoring. With over 115 publications in the field, he has had 13 Ph.D. students graduate under his supervision since he began teaching in 1996. He helped establish the International Networked Sensor Systems Conference (INSS), and served as editor for the leading MEMS publication, the IEEE/ASME Journal of Microelectromechanical Systems. Tien was also founder and chief technology officer of AIP Networks, an optical communication components company now part of Optoplex Corporation.\n\nPrior to CWRU, Tien served as chair of the Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering at the University of California at Davis and held a joint appointment at the University of California at Berkeley. He also served as co-director of the Berkeley Sensor &amp; Actuator Center. He previously held faculty positions in Cornell University’s Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering. Tien serves as a guest professor at Peking University and has received the distinction of honorary professor of Tianjin University in Tianjin, China.\n\nA National Science Foundation CAREER award recipient, Tien received his Ph.D. from the University of California at San Diego, his MS from the University of Illinois, and his BS from the University of California at Berkeley. He received the second annual Chang-Lin Tien Education Leadership Award that recognizes the accomplishments of rising Asian American leaders in higher education to support their professional development and advancement.
    </string>
    <string name="teinfo36">
    Dr. K.K.M. Tsia\n\nAssociate Professor\n\nPh.D., M.Phil., B.E.\nEmail:tsia@eee.hku.hk\nWeb: https://www.eee.hku.hk/~alphahku/\nTel.: 2857-8486\nOffice: CB 519\n\nResearch Interests\n\nUltrafast real-time optical microscopy and spectroscopy; nonlinear fiber optics; microfluidic bioassay technologies; High-throughput single-cell analysis.\n\nKevin Tsia received his Ph.D. degree at the Electrical Engineering Department, at University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA), in 2009. He is currently an Associate Professor in the Department of Electrical and Electronic Engineering, and the Medical Engineering Program, at the University of Hong Kong. His research interest covers a broad range of subject matters, including ultra-fast real-time spectroscopy and microscopy for biomedical applications such as imaging flow cytometry, MHz optical coherence tomography. His pervious researches, such as energy harvesting in silicon photonics and the World’s fastest barcode reader and optical imaging system, have attracted worldwide press coverage and featured in many prestigious science and technology review magazines such as MIT Technology Review, EE Times and Science News. Dr. Tsia was the recipient of a fellowship by the California Nanosystems Institute (CNSI) from 2005 to 2006. He also received the 2009 Harry M. Showman Prize from Henry Samueli School of Engineering and Applied Science at UCLA. He received Early Career Award 2012-2013 by the Research Grants Council (RGC) in Hong Kong. He received the Outstanding Young Research Award 2015 at HKU. His recent research on ultrafast optofluidic imaging technology, dubbed “ATOM”, has also been covered by local media and scientific magazines. He is author or coauthor of over 120 journal, conference papers and book chapters. He holds 2 granted and 2 pending US patents on ultrafast optical imaging technologies.

    </string>
    <string name="teinfo37">
    Prof. K.K.Y. Wong\n\nProfessor\n\nPh.D., M.Sc., B.E., B.Sc.\nEmail:kywong@eee.hku.hk\nWeb: https://www.eee.hku.hk/~kywong\nTel.: 2857-8483\nOffice: CB 718\n\nResearch Interests\n\nNovel optical generation; Photonic parametric processing; Ultrafast optical fiber communication and imaging (spectroscopy, microscopy and tomography). Prof. Kenneth Kin-Yip Wong received combined B.E. (1st class honor with medal award) degree in electrical engineering and B. S. degree in physics from the University of Queensland, Brisbane, Australia, in 1997. He received the M.S. degree in 1998 and the Ph.D. degree in 2003, both in electrical engineering at Stanford University. He was a member of the Photonics and Networking Research Laboratory at Stanford University. His research field included DWDM systems, SCM optical systems, fiber nonlinearity, and fiber optical parametric amplifiers. He is author or coauthor of over 50 journal and conference papers. He worked in Hewlett-Packard Laboratories as research engineer and contributed in projects included parallel optics and VCSEL in 1998-99. He also worked as independent consultant in Innovation CORE (A Sumitomo Electric Company), CA, in 2004. He was the recipient of OSA New Focus Student Award in 2003 and IEEE/LEOS Graduate Student Fellowship in 2003. He is the reviewer for Optics Letters, JOSA B, Optics Express, IEEE Photonics Technology Letters, IEEE/OSA Journal of Lightwave Technology and Optics Communications. Prof. Wong is currently a Professor in the Department of Electrical and Electronic Engineering in the University of Hong Kong. He is a senior member of the IEEE (Photonics Society), OSA, and SPIE.
    </string>
    <string name="teinfo38">
    Dr. N. Wong\n\nAssociate Professor\n\nPh.D.\nEmail:nwong@eee.hku.hk\nWeb: https://www.eee.hku.hk/~nwong\nTel.: 2859-1914\nOffice: CB 720\n\nResearch Interests\n\nVLSI model reduction, digital filter design, Sigma-Delta converters, antenna array, semidefinite programming and optimization techniques. Dr. N. Wong received his B.Eng. (first class honor) degree in 1999 and Ph.D. degree in 2003, both in Electrical and Electronic Engineering from The University of Hong Kong. From Jan 2003 to Sep 2003, he was a visiting scholar at the Purdue University, IN, USA, where he investigated VLSI related topics. From 1997 to 1998, he was a product engineer in Motorola Semiconductor Hong Kong Ltd. under an internship program, where he worked on mixed-signal IC design and circuit testing. His research interests include digital filter design with delta operator, filter optimization, Sigma-Delta modulator design and analysis, and the application of semidefinite programming in communication systems and VLSI synthesis. His current research focuses on VLSI model order reduction for computer-aided design, and the corresponding algorithmic development and electrical network synthesizing techniques.
    </string>
    <string name="teinfo39">
    Prof. E.X. Wu\n\nChair of Biomedical Engineering\nLam Woo Professorship in Biomedical Engineering\n\nBSEE Tianjin Univ.; MS Univ. of Wisconsin-Madison; Ph.D. Univ. of California-Irvine; F.I.S.M.R.M, F.I.E.E.E, F.A.I.M.B.E, F.H.K.I.E.\nEmail:ewu@eee.hku.hk\nTel.: 2859-7096\nOffice: CB 601G\n\nResearch Interests\n\nBiomedical imaging; magnetic resonance imaging (MRI) physics and engineering; preclincial and clinical MRI applications; neuroscience;\n\nProf. Ed X. Wu is Chair Professor of Biomedical Engineering and holds Lam Woo Professorship in Biomedical Engineering. He joined the University of Hong Kong Department of Electrical and Electronic Engineering in 2003. Before joining HKU, Prof. Wu was an Associate Professor of Radiology and Biomedical Engineering at Columbia University in New York where he led the NMR Microimaging Laboratory and served as a core member of Columbia Integrated Imaging Center. From 1990 to 1998, Prof. Wu was the lead technical member in development of the world first 3D positron emission tomography (PET) system and an ultrahigh field magnetic resonance imaging (MRI) system at Columbia University. At present, Prof. Wu is the founding Director of the interdisciplinary Laboratory of Biomedical Imaging and Signal Processing, and Research Director of 3T MRI Unit at HKU. He served as the Program Director of Medical Engineering Program from 2009 to 2013 and Associate Dean (Research) of HKU Faculty of Engineering from 2013 to 2016. His current research includes (1) biomedical imaging and medical instrumentation; and (2) development of advanced high-field and multi-modal MRI techniques for investigation of brain structures, functions and circuits. Prof. Wu is the recipient of numerous extramural research grants awarded by US National Institutes of Health (NIH), US Defense Advanced Research Projects Agency (DARPA), US Department of Interior and Hong Kong Research Grant Council (RGC).\n\nProf. Wu presently is the Asia-Pacific Editor of NMR in Biomedicine and an editorial board member of Magnetic Resonance in Medicine. He has served in numerous technical and scientific committees in professional societies, funding agencies and international conferences, including US NIH, Hong Kong RGC and ITC assessment panels. Prof. Wu is an elected Fellow of International Society for Magnetic Resonance in Medicine (ISMRM) in 2013, Institute of Electrical and Electronic Engineers (IEEE) in 2014, American Institute for Medical and Biological Engineering (AIMBE) in 2011, and Hong Kong Academy of Engineering Sciences (HKAES) in 2018. He is the recipient of 2009 Outstanding Researcher Award from HKU, 2012 Croucher Senior Research Fellowship from Croucher Foundation, and 2018 Guanghua Engineering Science and Technology Prize which is the highest national award from Chinese Academy of Engineering. Prof. Wu is the 2016-2017 President of Overseas Chinese Society for Magnetic Resonance in Medicine (OCSMRM).\n\nHe is an Honorary Professor at Departments of Medicine, Diagnostic Radiology, and School of Biomedical Sciences at HKU Li Ka Shing Faculty of Medicine.
    </string>
    <string name="teinfo40">
    Dr. J.C.H. Yuen\n\nLecturer\n\nB.Sc., M.Phil., Ph.D. CityU\nEmail:chyuen@eee.hku.hk\nTel.: 2859 7098\nOffice: CB 522\n\nDr. Joe Yuen received his BSc Hons in computer science in 1997, M.Phil. in 2000 and Ph.D. in 2005 at the City University of Hong Kong. He was an Instructor at the same University from 2001 to 2017. During this period, he dedicated himself in teaching and learning development. Dr. Yuen offered a wide range of courses including programming, networking, distributed system, mobile apps development, computer game design and AI game programming.   He is eager to apply different approaches to raise students’ interest in learning. He treats teaching as a serious process to transform and prepare student for the future world.   In 2008, he was the prior and deputy coordinator of Outcome Based Teaching in his department. He led several projects in mobile learning and being the coordinator of UGC Community of Practices (CoP): Technology and Creativity Community in CityU.   Joe was the Vice-Chairman of ACM HK Chapter from 2013 to 2017. Since September 2017 he joined the Department of Electrical and Electroinic Engineering, the University of Hong Kong (HKU), where he is a Lecturer.
    </string>
    <string name="teinfo41">
    Dr. J. Zhong\n\nAssociate Professor\n\nB.Sc. Tsinghua; M.Sc. EPRI, China; Ph.D. Chalmers.\nEmail:jzhong@eee.hku.hk\nTel.: 2857-8487\n\nResearch Interests\n\nElectricity market; power system economic operation; renewable energy; smart grid; micro grid.\n\nDr. J. Zhong received the B.Sc from Tsinghua University in 1995 and M. Sc from the Electric Power Research Institute, China in 1998. She received her Ph.D. degree from Chalmers University of Technology, Sweden in 2003. From June 2002 to Nov. 2002, she was a visiting scholar at Washington State University.
    </string>


    <!--FAQ, Frequency Asked Questions, 14 questions with their answer-->
    <!--Data from HKU Engineering Faculty MSc websites-->
    <string name="title_activity_faq">FAQ</string>

    <string name="fqt1">
       Q1: Can I apply for more than one taught postgraduate curriculum?
    </string>
    <string name="fq1">
       A: Yes, you can apply for more than one taught postgraduate curriculum. You should submit an online application and pay the application fee online for each application.
    </string>

    <string name="fqt2">
       Q2: How much is the application fee for taught postgraduate admissions and how should I pay for it?
    </string>
    <string name="fq2">
       A: The application fee for each application is HK$300 (non-refundable). Payment of application fee should be made online at https://hku.hk/tpg/. Payment by cash will NOT be accepted.
    </string>

    <string name="fqt3">
       Q3: When will the results of applications be announced?
    </string>
    <string name="fq3">
       A: The results for admission in September are normally available by July of the same year. Hence, applicants who do not hear from the Faculty of Engineering by July 31, 2019 may assume the application to be unsuccessful.
    </string>

    <string name="fqt4">
       Q4: If my application submission is incomplete, will it still be processed?
    </string>
    <string name="fq4">
       A: We cannot process your application unless the submission is complete. That means we must receive:\n&#x0009; the completed application form;\n&#x0009; the application fee of HK$300;\n&#x0009; ranscripts of all tertiary educational institutions attended; and\n&#x0009; the score report on English language proficiency test, if required.
    </string>

    <string name="fqt5">
       Q5: How can I submit the supporting documents for my application?
    </string>
    <string name="fq5">
       A: Applications will be considered based on the information provided. Therefore you are advised to upload all the supporting documents to the on-line application system upon application for admission to the MSc curriculum.\n\nIf you have already completed your undergraduate study, you are advised to upload all the information to the system.\n\nIf you have NOT completed your undergraduate study at the time of application, you are advised to upload the latest transcript of your current studies and all available information deemed relevant to your application to the system.\n\nIf you receive a conditional offer of admission subsequently, you have to submit the documents required including but not limited to the official / certified true copy of transcript to the Department concerned*Note by the deadline specified.\n
    </string>

    <string name="fqt6">
       Q6: If I submit multiple applications, how many sets of supporting documents shall I submit?
    </string>
    <string name="fq6">
       A: As the applications will be handled by different staff, one set of supporting documents should be submitted for EACH application.\n\nPART1: Uploading the application materials to the application system during application\n&#x009;Degree Certificates: Degree certificates awarded.\n&#x009;Transcripts: Upload all the final transcripts of your previous post-secondary studies, whether completed or not.\n        If you are currently a student, please also upload the latest transcript of your current studies.\n        (The back side of the transcript(s) should also be provided if it contains information on the grading system.)\n\n&#x009;Score Reports of English Language Proficiency Tests (e.g. IELTS, TOEFL): Upload the score reports (and remember to arrange the official score reports to be sent to us direct from the issuing authorities well before the scores expire). \n        If you plan to sit a test later, please provide the planned date. Update the scores and upload the score report when available.\n&#x009;Calculation of Academic Results: If your Cumulative Grade Point Average (CGPA) / average grade / average mark is not shown in the transcript, please use the template (http://engg.hku.hk/faculty_msc/calsheet.xls) to calculate (and remember to convert the file to JPEG for uploading).\n        If you are currently an undergraduate student, please also calculate CGPA / average grade / average mark obtained based on the latest available transcript.\n        If you have more than one qualification, please use a separate calculation sheet for each.\n\n\nPART2: Sending the supporting documents after you have received a conditional offer of admission.\n&#x009;Degree Certificates / Transcripts: Should you be given an admission offer by the University, you will be required to provide original / certified true copy of your documents. Please refer to the conditional offer letter for the required documents. \n\n        Do not send us irreplaceable documents. Instead, send certified true copies of certificates (if required) and ask your institutions to send your transcripts. \n\n        Certificates and transcripts which are not in English should be accompanied by an officially certified translation. \n\n        If completing a degree is part of your conditions of offer, you do not need to send the incomplete transcript which has already been uploaded but need to send the final transcript when you complete the studies. \n\n&#x009;We accept official score reports sent by issuing authorities only. Please arrange well before the scores expire.\n\n&#x009;If completing a degree is part of your conditions of offer, you need to re-calculate your CGPA / average grade / average mark using the results on the final transcript when you have completed your studies.\n\n

    </string>

    <string name="fqt7">
       Q7: Do I need to attach or send in academic / professional referees" reports?
    </string>
    <string name="fq7">
       A: You do NOT need to attach or send in academic / professional referees’ reports for your application for admission to MSc(Eng) / MSc curricula in the Faculty unless requested. If you still wish to provide us a reference letter, you may upload it via the online application system.\n
    </string>

    <string name="fqt8">
       Q8:If I am given a conditional offer by the University, are photocopies of the required documents acceptable to the University?
    </string>
    <string name="fq8">
       A: Please note that the University will only accept originals or copies of the documents that have been duly declared as true copies before a notary public (e.g. a Commissioner for Oaths at a District Office in Hong Kong). Copies of documents may be certified by the appropriate officials of your home institute if you are an overseas applicant.\n\nDocuments which are not in English should be accompanied by a formally certified translation in English.
    </string>

    <string name="fqt9">
       Q9: How can I get the officially certified true copies of transcripts of my undergraduate / postgraduate studies forwarded to the Department concerned*Note?
    </string>
    <string name="fq9">
       A: We recommend one of the two methods listed below: \n\ni) Simply complete the "Transcript Request Form" and directly send that form to the institution from which you graduated. That institution will then directly send certified copies of your transcripts to the Department concerned*Note.\n\nii) The Faculty also accepts photocopies of original documents that have been duly declared as true copies before a notary public (for example a Commissioner for Oaths at a City District Office in Hong Kong).\n
    </string>

    <string name="fqt10">
       Q10: Can I apply for transferring credit(s) for course(s) completed successfully at this / another university to be counted towards completion of the MSc(Eng) / MSc curriculum in HKU?\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="fq10">
       A: You can apply for counting up to 12 credits successfully completed at this or another university before admission to the MSc curriculum in HKU towards completion of the HKUMSc curriculum. Students who wish to do so should make the request upon application for admission by completing the relevant column in the application form and providing ALL the supporting documents.\nAny application made after admission to the HKU MSc curriculum in Engineering will NOT be considered.\n
    </string>

    <string name="fqt11">
       Q11: Is concurrent registration allowed in HKU?
    </string>
    <string name="fq11">
       A: Concurrent registration by a student of HKU for another postsecondary qualification either at HKU or at another institution is not permitted, unless approval of the Senate has been obtained in advance. A breach of this Regulation in Hong Kong or elsewhere may result in the student concerned being required to discontinue studies at this University.\n
    </string>

    <string name="fqt12">
       Q12: Will applications submitted after application deadline be considered?
    </string>
    <string name="fq12">
       A: Late applications will NOT be considered.
    </string>

    <string name="fqt13">
       Q13: Do I need to attach my undergraduate results with the application form if I am a graduate of The University of Hong Kong?
    </string>
    <string name="fq13">
       A: Yes. Please upload a photocopy of the transcript(s) or a photocopy of the printout of your examination results from the Student Information System (SIS).\n
    </string>

    <string name="fqt14">
       Q14: Is there any financial assistance provided to students admitted to the curriculum?
    </string>
    <string name="fq14">
       A: The following forms of financial assistance are available from the Hong Kong Government to eligible students who are Hong Kong residents:\n\n

        i) Continuing Education Fund (CEF) for eligible Hong Kong residents – Reimbursements of up to HK$10,000 upon completion of certain approved courses with an overall attendance rate no less than 70%. Please visit the CEF website at https://www.wfsfaa.gov.hk/cef for further details and updates of eligibility, application, and reimbursement procedures (in particular the reimbursement period from the date of application). \n\n

        ii) Financial Assistance Schemes administered by the Government Student Finance Office (SFO). Please visit https://www.wfsfaa.gov.hk/sfo for further details.\n

    </string>


    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fq1"></string>
    <string name="title_activity_fq2"></string>
    <string name="title_activity_fq3"></string>
    <string name="title_activity_fq4"></string>
    <string name="title_activity_fq5"></string>
    <string name="title_activity_fq6"></string>
    <string name="title_activity_fq7"></string>
    <string name="title_activity_fq8"></string>
    <string name="title_activity_fq9"></string>
    <string name="title_activity_fq10"></string>
    <string name="title_activity_fq11"></string>
    <string name="title_activity_fq12"></string>
    <string name="title_activity_fq13"></string>
    <string name="title_activity_fq14"></string>
    <!--the follow string are from Harriosn-->

    <string name="title_activity_entrance">EntranceActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_apply">ApplyActivity</string>

    <string name="sample_hide_log">Hide log</string>
    <string name="sample_show_log">Show log</string>

    <string name="app_pro">APP PRO</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="tab1txt">
        <![CDATA[
        Application materials are available online at:\nhttp://www.aal.hku.hk/tpg/.\n\nYou can submit your application and application fee, which is non-refundable and non-transferable,online at:\nhttp://www.aal.hku.hk/tpg/.\n\nPayment by cash will NOT be accepted.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="tab2txt">
        <![CDATA[
        Along with the application the following documents are required to be submitted:\n\nOfficially certified degree certificate(s) and transcript(s) of your graduate and undergraduate studies*\n\nOfficial score report on an English Language proficiency test, such as TOEFL or IELTS\n\nCompleted calculation sheet\n\nAveraged mark should also be provided using the calculation sheet and preferably be “certified by the attending University”.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="tab3txt">
        <![CDATA[
        Once an application has been received, it will be reviewed by the programme directors.\n\nThe application status and pending documents required will be highlighted\n\nin the online application status system (see below). Normally,\n\napplications in the main round will be processed in batches of every three weeks\n\nuntil the available quotas are filled to reduce processing delay.\n\nTherefore, applicants are urged to submit their applications together\n\nwith the relevant documents at their earliest convenience. Normally,\n\nwe shall only consider local applicants in the clearing round.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="tab4txt">
        <![CDATA[
        The status of each applicant and the pending documents will be highlighted in the online\n\napplication status system, which can be accessed at http://intranet.eee.hku.hk/mscstatus/default.htm.\n\nYou can also go to the home page and click Entrance to check the updated status.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="tab5txt">
        <![CDATA[
        Due to limited quotas available, only one offer will be given to a qualified applicant even\n\nif he/she has applied for two or more programs offered by a department.\n\nTherefore, applicants are urged to consider carefully before submitting multiple applications to the department.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="tab6txt">
        <![CDATA[
        Admission to the MSc (Eng) programs will start in October,\n\n2018. Applications will be processed in batches until the quota is filled. As places are limited,\n\napplicants are advised to apply online and provide the supporting documents as soon as possible.\n\nThe admission deadlines are:\n\nMain round: December 31, 2018\n\nClearing round: 12:00nn, April 15, 2019\n\nNote: Normally, only local applicants will be considered in the clearing round.
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="tab1tt">Application Procedures</string>
    <string name="tab2tt">Required Supporting Documents</string>
    <string name="tab3tt">Application Processing</string>
    <string name="tab4tt">Application Status</string>
    <string name="tab5tt">Selection of Programs</string>
    <string name="tab6tt">Application Timetable</string>


    <!--the upper string are from Harriosn-->
    <!--Terry is coming-->
    <string name="text_Definition_and_Terminology">Definition and Terminology</string>
    <string name="text_Curriculum_Structure">Curriculum Structure</string>
    <string name="text_Subject_Groups">Subject Groups</string>
    <string name="text_Dissertation_Information">Dissertation Information</string>
    <string name="text_expanded">Expanded</string>
    <string name="text_collapsed">Collapsed</string>


    <string-array name="string_array_Definition_and_Terminology">
        <item>Discipline course – any course on a list of courses in the discipline of curriculum which a candidate must pass at least a certain number of credits as specified in the Regulations.\n\nElective course – any course offered by the Departments of the Faculty of Engineering for the fulfilment of the curriculum requirements of the degree of MSc(Eng) in Electrical and Electronic Engineering that are not classified as discipline courses.\n\nCapstone Experience# – a 24-credit dissertation which is a compulsory and integral part of the curriculum.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="string_array_Curriculum_Structure">
        <item>Candidates are required to complete 72 credits of courses as set out below, normally over one academic year of full-time study or two academic years of part-time study:</item>
        <item>Discipline Courses [Not less than 30]\n\nElective Courses [Not more than 18]\n\nCapstone Experience [24]\n\nTotal [72]</item>
        <item>Candidates shall select courses in accordance with the regulations of the degree. Candidates must complete 8 courses and a dissertation. They may select no more than 3 courses from the other taught postgraduate curricula in the Faculty of Engineering as electives. All course selection will be subject to approval by the Course Coordinators.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="string_array_Subject_Groups">
        <item>Course Titles(A.General):\n\nFor the General Stream, candidates may choose from any of the three subject groups.</item>
        <item>Course Titles(B.Communications Engineering):\n\nTo qualify as a graduate of the Communications Engineering Stream, candidates must pass at least 5 discipline courses in the Communication Engineering subject group.</item>
        <item>Course Titles(C.Power Engineering):\n\nTo qualify as a graduate of the Power Engineering Stream, candidates must pass at least 5 discipline courses in the Power Engineering subject group.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="string_array_Dissertation_Information">
        <item>Each student is required to complete\n\ni.a dissertation under the supervision of an appropriate teacher(s) in this department\nAND\ii.nattend and satisfactorily complete a capstone workshop in his/her respective stream/programme.</item>
        <item>The overall performance of capstone will be solely determined by the dissertation.\n\nStudents failing in fulfilling the requirement (including attendance) of the workshop will need to be re-assessed or re-take the workshop.</item>
        <item>MSc(Eng) in EEE (Communications Engineering and General Stream)\n\ni.Embedded System using Field Programming Gate Arrays (FPGA)\nOR\nii.Apps Programming</item>
        <item>MSc(Eng) in EEE (Power Engineering Stream)\n\ni.Power Systems Simulation\nOR\nii.Power Electronics Simulation</item>
        <item>The workshops will normally be held in Part I Lab (LG-205, Chow Yei Ching Building) in the first 6 weeks of the first and second semesters (depending on the total number of students enrolled). In general, full-time students are given preference to take the workshop in the first semester while part-time students are given preference to take the workshop in the second semester. Details of re-assessment will be announced by instructors of the workshop.</item>
        <item>Students should first enroll in a dissertation capstone workshop (ELEC7021/EMEE7001) of their respective stream/programme in the online enrollment system. Meanwhile, students may contact the appropriate supervisors directly for more details about the dissertation or for self-proposed dissertation. Please visit the following link for possible dissertation topics offered by the EEE Department\n\nhttp://intranet.eee.hku.hk/mscproject/projlist.asp.</item>
        <item>The list will be updated by approximately in the middle of September each year. If both the supervisor and student agree to work on a given dissertation, the student should complete and return a dissertation supervisor confirmation form (which can be downloaded in the following link) to the Department.\n\nhttps://www.eee.hku.hk/download/msceng-in-eee-msceng-in-energye-dissertation-form/</item>
    </string-array>
    <!--Terry end-->
</resources>
